<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.6.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-04-09T15:41:37-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/</id><title type="html">CSCI376 Project: Art for All</title><subtitle>Collaborative platform for artistic engagement</subtitle><author><name>Art for All</name></author><entry><title type="html">Heuristic Evaluations</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/heuristic-evaluations/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Heuristic Evaluations" /><published>2018-04-09T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-04-09T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/heuristic-evaluations</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/heuristic-evaluations/">&lt;p&gt;Stephanie and Joyce facilitated an heuristic evaluation performed by Karl on our paper prototype (and vice versa for Pin’s prototype). His full evaluation is below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/heuristic-karl-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Karl&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Karl's written evaluation&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cliff facilitated an evaluation performed by Alyssa and Lester (and vice versa for Pin’s prototype). Their full evaluations are below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/heuristic-alyssa-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Alyssa&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Alyssa's written evaluation&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/heuristic-lester-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lester&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Lester's written evaluation&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An overview image of the paper prototype we used for evaluation is also shown below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper_prototyping_overview.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Overview&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Components of paper prototype&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To see the evaluations we performed on Pin’s paper prototype, please refer to Pin’s project page.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Paper Prototyping</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/paper-prototype/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Paper Prototyping" /><published>2018-04-04T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-04-04T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/paper-prototype</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/paper-prototype/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;design&quot;&gt;Design&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Art for All is a mobile application that allows users to learn more about the art pieces users see in museums&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tasks&quot;&gt;Tasks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Learn more context and background information to better understand the meaning behind artworks&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Discuss artwork with others in order further engage with the pieces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;overview-of-paper-prototyping&quot;&gt;Overview of paper prototyping&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper_prototyping_overview.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Overview&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Components of paper prototype&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The application has three primary modes: the museum profile, search, and user profile. The yellow highlighted box indicates which mode the user is in. Initially opening the application brings the user to the default Search mode page, as shown in Screen 1.1. From this page, users have the option between either a text search, as shown in Screens 1.2, 1.3, or a picture QR code search, as shown in Screens 1.4, 1.5, 1.6 Both lead to a results page, in Screen 1.7, where the desired artwork can be chosen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper_prototyping_ search.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Search&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Searching artwork&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clicking on the artwork opens a nested art profile page with “About” (Screen 2.1), “Learn More,” and “Discussion” tabs the user can toggle between to support the first task of discovering more context about artworks. The “Learn More” tab (Screen 2.3) contains drop-down menus of further background information, including “Context,” “Inspiration,” “History,” and “Genre” that can be collapsed and expanded, as shown in Screen 2.5.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper_prototyping_ art_profile_1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Art Prof 1&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Artwork Profile&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper_prototyping_ art_profile_2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Art Prof 2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Artwork Profile (cont.)&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The “Discussion” tab (Screen 2.7) supports the task of discussing art with others. In this tab, users can post and reply to other users’ comments about this artwork, as shown in Screens 2.8-12.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper_prototyping_ user_profile.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;User Profile&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;User Profile&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clicking on the User Profile mode displays the initial Screen 3.1. The user profile displays a header containing a user profile picture, name, and bio. The body of the page consist of “Favorites” and “Threads” tabs that are toggled between. The “Favorites” tab displays favorited artworks. Clicking on any of these artworks, in Screen 3.2, brings the user to a nested art profile page, in Screen 3.3. The “Threads” tab (Screen 3.5) displays a list of discussions the user has participated in and highlights those with unread replies. Clicking on any of these comments, in Screen 3.6, opens a nested discussion page, as shown in Screen 3.7.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Final Report</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Final-Report/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Final Report" /><published>2018-04-04T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-04-04T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Final-Report</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Final-Report/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;project&quot;&gt;Project&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Art for All: An interactive and educational platform for public engagement at art museums&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;team-members-all-generalists&quot;&gt;Team Members (all generalists):&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cliff Makanda, Stephanie Liu, Joyce Wang&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;problem-and-solution-overview&quot;&gt;Problem and Solution Overview:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Art museums have long been a primary resource for learning about and experiencing art. Unfortunately, art can often feel intimidatingly inaccessible for the general public. For regular people, who aren’t academics or involved in the “art world,” art can feel elusive, out-of-touch, or even perhaps just confusing. Without a formal introduction to art, which is generally only available to the privileged, it becomes difficult to glean much insight from abstract and unfamiliar artworks. This problem stems from both the little information museums provide about artworks as well as the lack of informal resources available for engaging in conversations about art. Art for All intends to overcome these hurdles by providing a simple and easy-to-use framework for finding background information about artworks and artists, and allowing users to engage in informal discussions about specific artworks online. In this way, users from a diverse set of backgrounds can come together to discuss their varied interpretations of art to get a better understanding of how art can impact their lives. In addition, background information will be readily accessible and easy to understand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;design-research-goals-stakeholders-and-participants&quot;&gt;Design Research: Goals, Stakeholders, and Participants&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This &lt;a href=&quot;../design-research-goals-stakeholders-and-participants&quot;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; provides information about the methods and process we used for gathering design research through interviews and contextual inquiries, as well as detailed accounts of the participants, their backgrounds, and the environments in which they were interviewed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;design-research-results-and-themes&quot;&gt;Design Research: Results and Themes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This &lt;a href=&quot;../design-research-results-and-themes&quot;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; provides an overview of the key results and themes from our design research, as found through affinity diagramming. The emergence of these key themes allowed us to guide our design to specifically tailor user needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;task-analysis&quot;&gt;Task Analysis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This &lt;a href=&quot;../task-analysis&quot;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; details our answers to specific task analysis questions, and allows us to set the scope of our design as it relates to the users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;proposed-design-sketches-3x4&quot;&gt;Proposed Design Sketches (“3x4”)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This &lt;a href=&quot;../Proposed-Design-Sketches-3-x-4&quot;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; presents three different potential design choices, and details the specific tasks they are designed to support. An updated design is presented at the end, with an explanation for why that specific design was ultimately chosen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;written-scenarios-1x2&quot;&gt;Written Scenarios (“1x2”)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This &lt;a href=&quot;../Written-Scenarios-1-x-2&quot;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; details the two selected tasks we chose to support in our final design, and written scenarios for each task that correspond to the storyboards as presented in the next section.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;storyboards&quot;&gt;Storyboards&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This &lt;a href=&quot;../Storyboards&quot;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; presents the two storyboards that correspond to our selected tasks.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Storyboards</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Storyboards/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Storyboards" /><published>2018-03-12T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-03-12T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Storyboards</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Storyboards/">&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/storyboard-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Storyboard 1&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Storyboard 1: Finding background information task &lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/storyboard-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Storyboard 2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Storyboard 2: Participating in online discussions about art task&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Written Scenarios (“1x2”)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Written-Scenarios-1-x-2/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Written Scenarios (“1x2”)" /><published>2018-03-11T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-03-11T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Written-Scenarios-1-x-2</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Written-Scenarios-1-x-2/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;selected-supported-tasks&quot;&gt;Selected Supported Tasks&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our two selected tasks are finding background information about an artwork, and engaging in online discussions focused on specific artworks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finding background information is an activity that is central to the museum experience. We found during our contextual inquiries that all of the people we talked to came to the museum to learn about art, although some emphasized different aspects of that learning. In either case, we definitely wanted to highlight this learning aspect in our app.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the discussion side, we mostly interviewed people who were already in groups, and we noticed how they enjoyed talking to each other about the art as they went along. The discussion task will thus allow for a wider conversation to take place with a more diverse set of people. In addition, people who find themselves visiting a museum alone will still get to discuss their experience with others. Art is a social experience. A museum-goer should not only be able to communicate with an artwork but also with other museum-goers. This allows for cross pollination of ideas and different interpretations of art.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;scenarios&quot;&gt;Scenarios&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;scenario-1-finding-background-information&quot;&gt;Scenario 1: Finding background information&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ben is visiting his local art museum and comes across a piece that really strikes him. He wants to know more, so he pulls up the Art for All app and navigates to the search tab. He clicks on the camera button and scans a picture of the QR code on the artworks’ panel. The app pulls up the artworks’ profile, and he clicks on the Learn More tab. He wants to learn about the inspiration for the piece, so he clicks on the Inspiration section and reads about the artists’ inspiration for the work. When he has read as much info as he’d like to know, he closes the app and moves on to investigate more in the museum. See &lt;a href=&quot;../Storyboards&quot;&gt;Storyboard 1&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;scenario-2-discussing-art&quot;&gt;Scenario 2: Discussing Art&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bob has recently visited a museum and become entranced with a Jackson Pollock work. He is waiting for the bus, and thinks back to this piece. He decides he wants to discuss this particular artwork with others, so he pulls up the Art for All app and navigates to the discussion section under this artwork profile page. He asks some probing questions, and finds that another student, Sarah, is also online at the same time and wants to talk about this particular work. They discuss their interpretations, and in the end Bob feels like he has a better understanding of the artwork. See &lt;a href=&quot;../Storyboards&quot;&gt;Storyboard 2&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Proposed Design Sketches (“3x4”)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Proposed-Design-Sketches-3-x-4/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Proposed Design Sketches (“3x4”)" /><published>2018-03-07T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-03-07T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Proposed-Design-Sketches-3-x-4</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Proposed-Design-Sketches-3-x-4/">&lt;p&gt;Note: See the &lt;a href=&quot;../Supported-Tasks&quot;&gt;supported tasks&lt;/a&gt; page for information about the tasks referenced here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;first-design&quot;&gt;First Design&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/steph-sketch-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Stephanie’s Sketch&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Sketch of first design&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tasks:&lt;/strong&gt; Background information, contexts, discussion, favoriting, and remembering&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Main Idea:&lt;/strong&gt; This design focuses on how we might layout a particular “art profile” and the discovery of new information about the artwork, as well as user and artist profiles. The artwork is presented as a central page, where “about”, “learn more”, and “discussion” are the main focuses and the user can tab between them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Tasks 1 &amp;amp; 4) Learning:&lt;/strong&gt; The “about” tab includes a placard-like explanation. The “learn more” tab on the artwork’s profile allows the user to make an individual choice about which aspect of the background information she’d like to explore through a series of tabbed pages. Elliot, who likes history, can specifically choose the history tab. In addition, there is a small “progress bar” at the bottom that allows the user to navigate to more information if their curiosity is not yet satisfied. Logan, who wants to learn about the inspiration, can navigate to the “inspiration” section.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Tasks 2, 5, 8) &lt;em&gt;Discussion:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; The “discussion” tab on the artwork’s profile allows the users to talk with each other and with scholars and artists in the field to learn about the artwork in a more informal/colloquial setting. Both Anna and Caroline can use this functionality to hear about others’ experiences. The scholars/artists who participate in the discussion will have special annotations on their icons to indicate that they are professionals in their field, and the particular artist of the work will have a distinct icon so they can reliably answer questions that come up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Task 6) &lt;em&gt;Favoriting Artworks:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; On the “art profile,” there is a button on the upper-right corner (the heart) that allows the users to favorite the work they are looking at. In addition, on the user profile page, Chelsea can look through her past favorites in the “favorites” tab, and also look at an overview of what her favorite pieces were like in the “about” tab. The “about” tab will show her what the breakdown of her favorite artworks is, by genre, time period, or possibly any number of things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Task 3) &lt;em&gt;Remembering Artworks:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; In the user profile, there will be a tab for “favorites.” The user can then look through the artworks they favorited and reflect on what they’ve enjoyed the most in the past. Carlos can use this functionality to keep tabs on all his favorite works, and learn more about them from the comfort of his own home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;second-design&quot;&gt;Second Design&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tasks:&lt;/strong&gt; finding background information, breaking down formal art terms, getting more context,
artist communicating with people about the work&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Main Idea:&lt;/strong&gt; This design is museum-centric. The mobile application is museum-specific and primarily for real-time use while visiting museums. The design allows users to more easily access information about art pieces that are sometimes available in museums, currently in the form of wall text and pamphlets, but now more directly in a centralized source. It provides streamlined, simple information about the piece. This design provides a text search option, a QR code search option, favorites page, and a location-based map of the museum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/joyce-sketch-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Joyce’s Sketch&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Sketch of second design: Main navigation&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Task 1) &lt;em&gt;Reading placards and finding background information about artworks:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
The search and QR scan options allow users to quickly find the pages for artworks. All artwork pages include an image of the work and ID information, such as title, artist, date, etc, that might usually be placed on placards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/joyce-sketch-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Joyce’s Sketch 2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Sketch of second design: Art Profile&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Tasks 1 &amp;amp; 4) &lt;em&gt;Understanding more context about art pieces:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
Scrolling down the Artwork Page reveals a two-tab menu option with “Description” (a brief analysis/explanation of the work) and “Artist” (an artist’s statement on the piece). Elliot and Logan can choose the “Description” tab when they want to learn more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Task 7) &lt;em&gt;Breaking down formal art interpretations into understandable terms:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
The “Description” tab also includes links to basic terms, such as “Surrealism,” which links to a nested page with a definition of the term in easy-to-understand language that Syd can use to develop more understanding about art.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Task 8) &lt;em&gt;Artist communicating to people interested in her work:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
The artist tab includes what the artist would like his/her audience to know about the specific work. Jordan can use this to explain additional information if questions come up. If the artist is current enough, the artist name links to a nested Artist Page, where background information about the artist is provided.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;third-design&quot;&gt;Third Design&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/cliff-sketch-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Cliff’s Sketch&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Sketch of third design&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tasks:&lt;/strong&gt; Understanding more context about art, discussing art with museum experts and novices, Finding background information about art.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Main Idea:&lt;/strong&gt; This design is focused connecting the artist to the museum-goer to enhance the latter’s understanding of an artist’s work. It also introduces a digital space to chat with the artist, other museum-goers, and art experts. The design is designed to be mobile-centric.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Task 4) &lt;em&gt;Understanding Context:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; The main page shows an artist’s profile. It goes into more depth than the traditional wall text or placard. At the top of the page is the artists name, below that we have the image of the artist. The image is followed by a link to the artist’s works. A brief but thorough description of the artist forms the main content of the page. A museum goer like Logan can get more context about an artwork by getting insights from the artists biography.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Task 1) &lt;em&gt;Background Information:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; After clicking the “works” link indicated above, a user is presented with a picture gallery of all the works by an artist. A user like Elliot who wants to understand the background of an artwork can see an artist’s work in relation to other works by the same artist. Clicking on an artwork will further lead to a page about the artwork that offers more detail and context.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Task 2) &lt;em&gt;Discussion with fellow museum-goers:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Below an artwork’s description is a chat bubble with a link that leads to a digital space that fosters discussion among the artist, museum-goers, and scholars in the field. The user is able to ask questions about an artwork and respond to other users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Task 5 &amp;amp; 8) &lt;em&gt;Discussion with experts and artist:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; On top of the discussion page is a list of most recent answers from an artist. Below that is a list of experts. A user can read past discussion and post questions. He is able to interact with both the artist and experts (if he chooses to).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;updated-design&quot;&gt;Updated Design&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We decided to combine parts of each of the first two designs in our final design. The second museum-centered design will serve as the basis for our app’s structure. The motivation for this choice came from our contextual inquiries, because we realized that most people don’t actually look at or find art on their own; they come to museums for that purpose. We chose to keep the map from the second design because our contextual inquiries revealed that navigating effectively through museums and from one exhibit to the next can be a challenge for people. We also kept the QR codes featured in that design, because we noticed when visiting MASS MoCA that many modern exhibits these days aren’t just framed artworks, so they would be harder to detect by just snapping a picture. In addition, some exhibits don’t allow camera use inside, so the QR code could be placed just outside the exhibit with the wall text. From the first design, we wanted to keep the tabs that toggle between “About”, “Learn More” and “Discussion,” because we didn’t feel like there was a streamlined sequence of events for people when viewing an artwork (i.e. they didn’t first read the background, then ask questions, and then discuss the art; they often went back and forth).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/updated-design-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Updated Interface&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/updated-design-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Updated Interface&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Updated Design&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;!--## Citations
1. [Dorothea Lange's &quot;Migrant Mother&quot; Photographs in the Farm Security Administration Collection: An Overview](http://www.loc.gov/rr/print/list/128_migm.html)--&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Supported Tasks</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Supported-Tasks/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Supported Tasks" /><published>2018-03-06T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-03-06T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Supported-Tasks</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Supported-Tasks/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;existing-tasks&quot;&gt;Existing Tasks:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;1-reading-placards-and-finding-background-information-about-artworks---hard-task&quot;&gt;1. &lt;em&gt;Reading placards and finding background information about artworks&lt;/em&gt; - Hard task&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Elliot is a junior majoring in history at Amherst. He likes going to museums to learn about history from a visual perspective, and he decides to attend a local art museum on the weekend. He sees an 18th century piece he really likes and reads the placard, but it names only the artist, date, and title of the work, and there is only explanatory wall text for the featured exhibits. He appreciates the art for what it is but feels he is missing part of the puzzle by not knowing anything about the connection between the artist and the work, and especially the history behind it. He writes down the name of the artwork for later, and continues on. When he returns from the museum, he googles the title of the piece hoping to learn more about it. Unfortunately, the artwork he liked so much was made by a lesser-known artist, so there isn’t much on the Internet about it. He does find a few scholarly articles about the artist, but they’re filled with confusing language and art terminology that he doesn’t understand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;2-discussing-art-with-others-in-person---moderate-task&quot;&gt;2. &lt;em&gt;Discussing art with others in person&lt;/em&gt; - Moderate task&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anna is a frequent attender of museums, and likes to explore new kinds of art. She visits a contemporary art exhibit with a group of friends in a new city. As they’re walking around, a passer-by suggests they go up close to look at the exhibit featuring mirrors, because it provides a different perspective. As they take turns looking at themselves in the reflections, they share thoughts about the experience, and they notice that they all have different opinions on the installation based on their experiences with looking at their own reflections. They feel they have learned about themselves, about each other, and about the power of art to make us think about ourselves, through this discussion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;3-appreciating-and-remembering-art-after-a-museum-visit---easy-task&quot;&gt;3. &lt;em&gt;Appreciating and remembering art after a museum visit&lt;/em&gt; - Easy task&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Carlos loves visiting museums, and he finds that certain artworks spark something in him that he just can’t describe. For these pieces, he tries to write them down somewhere so he can remember them for later–sometimes in a journal, sometimes in his “Notes” app on his phone. If the piece is part of a permanent exhibit, he jots that down too so he can visit it again the next time he comes to that museum. He also sometimes buys postcards or artist booklets at the museum so he can appreciate the art and look back on it even after he’s left the museum, but those can get pretty expensive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;new-tasks&quot;&gt;New Tasks:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;4-understanding-more-context-about-art-pieces---hard-task&quot;&gt;4. &lt;em&gt;Understanding more context about art pieces&lt;/em&gt; - Hard task&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Logan is visiting New York and decides to visit the famous MoMA, but he doesn’t know much about art and has no formal art training. He’s looking at the famous “Migrant Mother” photograph, and the placard notes that it was taken in 1963 in Nipomo, California by Dorothea Lange, but he gets no other information. He can feel the desperation in the image, but wants to learn more. Who is the woman in the photograph and why does she look like she’s suffering? He navigates to the photograph’s profile on the app and reads some basic information about the artwork. He learns that Lange was spending a month photographing migratory farm labor when she took this shot. He reads Lange’s account of her experience, and learns that the mother in the photograph “said that they had been living on frozen vegetables from the surrounding fields, and birds that the children killed. She had just sold the tires from her car to buy food.”&lt;sup&gt;[1]&lt;/sup&gt; Logan feels like he can now better understand the emotional energy of the photograph.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;5-discussing-art-with-museum-experts-and-novices---moderate-task&quot;&gt;5. &lt;em&gt;Discussing art with museum experts and novices&lt;/em&gt; - Moderate task&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Caroline is a flight attendant for a major airline company. Every now and then she finds herself stuck in a major city with nothing to do. To pass the time before her next assignment, she often visits museums. She does not have any formal background in art, and would rather spend her time at home with her children than reading books on art. Because she’s usually away for work in random cities, she doesn’t always have friends to go to museums with, but she still wants to discuss the art with “regular” people and potentially scholars if they use colloquial language. At her next stop in Toledo, she visits an art museum, and finds a really interesting abstract art piece that she doesn’t quite understand. She doesn’t really want to spend time reading about background information; she finds that process kind of boring. Instead, she navigates to the artwork’s profile on the app, and reads about other people’s experiences with the piece. She is fascinated with how others describe their experiences with art, and the language they use to convey their emotions. She is also impressed by the insights she gains by reading responses from scholars who use colloquial language. She is surprised to find that people took on very varied interpretations of the art, and slowly begins to develop the confidence to decide for herself what the artwork means to her. She even adds her own comment, and feels pride in participating in this discussion and adding her own take.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;6-favoriting-artworks---easy-task&quot;&gt;6. &lt;em&gt;Favoriting artworks&lt;/em&gt; - Easy task&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chelsea is an avid art-lover, and loves visiting art museums in her spare time. She visits a new museum that just opened in her city, and stumbles upon a painting that she is immediately entranced by. She wants to remember this artwork somehow, so that she can look back on it later and remember how it made her feel. She uses the app to navigate to the painting’s profile and “favorite” it. That night at home, she thinks more about the painting and other artworks that have impacted her. She pulls up the app to see all of the artworks she’s favorited in the past. She goes through some of them, and nostalgically remembers how she felt at each time, and even thinks about the context in her life when each of these artworks was particularly meaningful to her. As she scrolls through, she notices that most of the artworks she’s favorited have been paintings and abstract art, and feels like she’s learned something about her own personal style of expression through this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;extra-tasks&quot;&gt;Extra Tasks:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;7-breaking-down-formal-art-interpretations-into-understandable-terms---hard-task-existing&quot;&gt;7. &lt;em&gt;Breaking down formal art interpretations into understandable terms&lt;/em&gt; - Hard task (Existing)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Syd has had no formal experience studying art and so is not familiar with the formal terms used to describe art. However, she enjoys going to art museums on the weekend with her friends. On one visit, the pamphlets about the artworks use a lot of formal language she doesn’t understand. She asks her friends what they mean. However, there are some parts that are not understandable to her friends either. In these cases, she uses her phone to google each term, and after identifying appropriate definitions, she is able to piece together what the pamphlet is talking about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;8-artist-communicating-with-people-interested-in-her-work---moderate-task-new&quot;&gt;8. &lt;em&gt;Artist communicating with people interested in her work&lt;/em&gt; - Moderate task (New)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jordan Mitchell is a rising modern artist with a number of nationwide exhibitions. Her artwork is revolutionary and can be hard to understand for both art novices and experts. She often attends museum events, explains her work, and interacts with people interested in her work. However, she is unable to attend as many events as she would like to. She communicates with both novice and experienced museum goers. She is able to explain her work, and respond to any of their questions. This helps breakdown the barriers preventing people to understand her revolutionary artwork. It is also a way for Jordan to get real time feedback on how people see her artworks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;citations&quot;&gt;Citations&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.loc.gov/rr/print/list/128_migm.html&quot;&gt;Dorothea Lange’s “Migrant Mother” Photographs in the Farm Security Administration Collection: An Overview&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Task Review</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/task-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Task Review" /><published>2018-03-04T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-03-04T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/task-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/task-review/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;existing-tasks&quot;&gt;Existing Tasks:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;reading-placards-and-finding-background-information-about-artworks---hard-task&quot;&gt;Reading placards and finding background information about artworks - Hard task&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Elliot is a junior majoring in history at Amherst. He likes going to museums to learn about history from a visual perspective, and he decides to attend a local art museum on the weekend. He sees an 18th century piece he really likes and reads the placard, but it names only the artist, date, and title of the work, and there is only explanatory wall text for the featured exhibits. He appreciates the art for what it is but feels he is missing part of the puzzle by not knowing anything about the connection between the artist and the work, and especially the history behind it. He writes down the name of the artwork for later, and continues on. When he returns from the museum, he googles the title of the piece hoping to learn more about it. Unfortunately, the artwork he liked so much was made by a lesser-known artist, so there isn’t much on the Internet about it. He does find a few scholarly articles about the artist, but they’re filled with confusing language and art terminology that he doesn’t understand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;discussing-art-with-others-in-person---moderate-task&quot;&gt;Discussing art with others in person - Moderate task&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anna is a frequent attender of museums, and likes to explore new kinds of art. She visits a contemporary art exhibit with a group of friends in a new city. As they’re walking around, a passer-by suggests they go up close to look at the exhibit featuring mirrors, because it provides a different perspective. As they take turns looking at themselves in the reflections, they share thoughts about the experience. Her friend Trevor comments that seeing his reflection in a kaleidoscope way makes him feel uneasy; he’s not used to looking at himself so closely and from so many different angles at the same time. Anna notes that looking at her face within an art installation forces her to view herself in new ways. She feels like she’s looking at herself from an outsider’s perspective. Her friend Jenny then asks a museum staffer how the installation was created, and they have a discussion about where the installation is from and how it was installed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;appreciating-and-remembering-art-after-a-museum-visit---easy-task&quot;&gt;Appreciating and remembering art after a museum visit - Easy task&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Carlos loves visiting museums, and he finds that certain artworks spark something in him that he just can’t describe. For these pieces, he tries to write them down somewhere so he can remember them for later–sometimes in a journal, sometimes in his “Notes” app on his phone. If the piece is part of a permanent exhibit, he jots that down too so he can visit it again the next time he comes to that museum. He also sometimes buys postcards or artist booklets at the museum so he can appreciate the art and look back on it even after he’s left the museum, but those can get pretty expensive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;new-tasks&quot;&gt;New Tasks:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;understanding-more-context-about-art-pieces---hard-task&quot;&gt;Understanding more context about art pieces - Hard task&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Logan is visiting New York and decides to visit the famous MoMA, but he doesn’t know much about art and has no formal art training. He’s looking at the famous “Migrant Mother” photograph, and the placard notes that it was taken in 1963 in Nipomo, California by Dorothea Lange, but he gets no other information. He can feel the desperation in the image, but wants to learn more. Who is the woman in the photograph and why does she look like she’s suffering? He navigates to the photograph’s profile on the app and reads some basic information about the artwork. He learns that Lange was spending a month photographing migratory farm labor when she took this shot. He reads Lange’s account of her experience, and learns that the mother in the photograph “said that they had been living on frozen vegetables from the surrounding fields, and birds that the children killed. She had just sold the tires from her car to buy food.”&lt;sup&gt;[1]&lt;/sup&gt; Logan feels like he can now better understand the emotional energy of the photograph.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;discussing-art-with-museum-experts-and-novices---moderate-task&quot;&gt;Discussing art with museum experts and novices - Moderate task&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Caroline is a flight attendant for a major airline company. Every now and then she finds herself stuck in a major city with nothing to do. To pass the time before her next assignment, she often visits museums. She does not have any formal background in art, and would rather spend her time at home with her children than reading books on art. Because she’s usually away for work in random cities, she doesn’t always have friends to go to museums with, but she still wants to discuss the art with “regular” people who aren’t scholars or curators. At her next stop in Toledo, she visits an art museum, and finds a really interesting abstract art piece that she doesn’t quite understand. She doesn’t really want to spend time reading about background information; she finds that process kind of boring. Instead, she navigates to the artwork’s profile on the app, and reads about other people’s experiences with the piece. She is fascinated with how others describe their experiences with art, and the language they use to convey their emotions. She is surprised to find that people took on very varied interpretations of the art, and slowly begins to develop the confidence to decide for herself what the artwork means to her. She even adds her own comment, and feels pride in participating in this discussion and adding her own take.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;favoriting-artworks---easy-task&quot;&gt;Favoriting artworks - Easy task&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chelsea is an avid art-lover, and loves visiting art museums in her spare time. She visits a new museum that just opened in her city, and stumbles upon a painting that she is immediately entranced by. She wants to remember this artwork somehow, so that she can look back on it later and remember how it made her feel. She uses the app to navigate to the painting’s profile and “favorite” it. That night at home, she thinks more about the painting and other artworks that have impacted her. She pulls up the app to see all of the artworks she’s favorited in the past. She goes through some of them, and nostalgically remembers how she felt at each time, and even thinks about the context in her life when each of these artworks was particularly meaningful to her. As she scrolls through, she notices that most of the artworks she’s favorited have been paintings and abstract art, and feels like she’s learned something about her own personal style of expression through this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;citations&quot;&gt;Citations&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.loc.gov/rr/print/list/128_migm.html&quot;&gt;Dorothea Lange’s “Migrant Mother” Photographs in the Farm Security Administration Collection: An Overview&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Task Analysis</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/task-analysis/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Task Analysis" /><published>2018-02-28T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-02-28T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/task-analysis</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/task-analysis/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;1-who-is-going-to-use-the-design&quot;&gt;1. Who is going to use the design?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our main target users will be people who are interested in art and enjoy going to museums, but don’t necessarily have any formal background or training in art. We would also like to target users who study art formally, such as students, Art History professors and researchers, etc. We think their input will provide a valuable source of information for the general discussions on artworks, and may help guide the conversations in more productive ways. Lastly, we may want to involve museum curators in the process, to allow them to tailor “art profiles” based on the layouts of the exhibits and to provide relevant information (the same kind of information they might currently provide in pamphlets scattered throughout the museum). This would be an extension on the design, time permitting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;2-what-tasks-do-they-now-perform&quot;&gt;2. What tasks do they now perform?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the museum, users are currently able to glean information from placards, wall text/artist bios, and pamphlets. They can engage with the art in a more social way by talking to their friends, other museum-goers (if they are out-going people), or museum staff. Outside the museum, users interested in art might perform informal individual searches on art pieces or artists to learn extra information. Museum curators are responsible for putting together exhibits, deciding what kinds of information to put in artists bios and placards and what to leave out, and deciding whether to include additional pamphlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;3-what-tasks-are-desired&quot;&gt;3. What tasks are desired?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Users should be able to gain new knowledge about different pieces of art at their own pace. Users should be able to learn about artists, their inspiration, and any other relevant information about the piece. Users should be able to comment on artworks, read about others’ perspectives, and reply to others’ comments to spark a conversation. Users should be able to individualize their experience and feel personally connected to the art. This could mean being able to save artworks as “favorites,” or something else. Curators should be able to update information about exhibits, remove intolerant comments, provide helpful background information, and engage with the users themselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;4-how-are-the-tasks-learned&quot;&gt;4. How are the tasks learned?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because our product will be in the form of a mobile/web application, the learning process for users should be relatively straightforward. We will try to make the interface similar to other social interfaces to make the adoption very seamless. However, because this is an app for all ages, the tasks may also be learned at the museum (museum staff could be trained to teach a basic outline of how to use the app, if needed). If the museum curator aspect gets more complicated, learning will be at the design level (e.g. a short tutorial at the beginning).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;5-where-are-the-tasks-performed&quot;&gt;5. Where are the tasks performed?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The main focus will be users using the app while navigating museums, but there are additional use cases where the user might want to look back on exhibits he’s viewed in the past and comment on them, so we don’t restrict location. In addition, users may want to use the data as a resource for learning outside the museum. Curators will naturally be performing tasks at the museum or in their offices when planning out new exhibits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;6-what-is-the-relationship-between-the-person-and-data&quot;&gt;6. What is the relationship between the person and data?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because this is an online forum and we would like to limit intolerant behavior, comments will be public and linked to the person’s profile, but we will collect limited data about the person, and only as much as the user is willing to provide (we will not require much). The data regarding user comments should persist at least throughout the lifetime of the exhibit, and may be archived after. The data the museum curator provides (through background information, pictures, etc.) can be controlled by the curator herself, and she may archive or delete the data as she sees fit. Data should be updated frequently to bring up the newest comments and spark ongoing conversation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;7-what-other-tools-does-the-person-have&quot;&gt;7. What other tools does the person have?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Placards and pamphlets throughout museums are the current tools people have to learn new information about art and artists in museums. In addition, they have museum staff and other museum-goers to talk to. To establish individual relationships with art, users currently can buy postcards at museum gift shops as memorabilia of their favorite works. To learn additional information, users can also look up background information on artists or exhibits on their phone, but this may be a rather inefficient way of finding the relevant information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;8-how-do-people-communicate-with-each-other&quot;&gt;8. How do people communicate with each other?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Users will be able to leave comments, similar to comments sections in other social places (like Reddit, Youtube, etc.). They will be able to reply to others’ comments, start new comment threads, and read others’ perspectives. Users who have studied art formally will play a special role in this conversation, and may help guide the discussion or else inform the discussion with relevant background.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;9-how-often-are-the-tasks-performed&quot;&gt;9. How often are the tasks performed?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From our survey data, people seem to visit museums once a month to once a year, and this is when we’d expect people to perform the tasks most often. For museum curators, exhibits change frequently and the curators may want to regularly catch up with how users are reacting to their different exhibits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;10-what-are-the-time-constraints-on-the-tasks&quot;&gt;10. What are the time constraints on the tasks?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There aren’t any hard constraints on the tasks here, but since people spend limited time at a museum, they will likely not spend too much time on each individual “art profile.” How much time they do choose to spend will depend on the complexity of the art piece to the user and how interested the user is in that particular work. For the museum curators, there also won’t be any hard constraints, but we imagine they will want to be able to complete their tasks quickly and smoothly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;11-what-happens-when-things-go-wrong&quot;&gt;11. What happens when things go wrong?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fake news (spreading of false information masquerading as facts), conversations devolving into mere speculations rather than a genuine understanding of the art, and intolerant behavior or hate speech that is unproductive and uninformative (trolls).&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Design Research Results and Themes</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/design-research-results-and-themes/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Design Research Results and Themes" /><published>2018-02-28T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-02-28T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/design-research-results-and-themes</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/design-research-results-and-themes/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;key-findings-and-results&quot;&gt;Key Findings and Results&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through our research, we uncovered a lot of information about people’s experience with art. We learned that people often view art in relation to their lives. Many people with no formal art background interact with art by drawing similarities to different aspects of their lives. We also learned that direction is sometimes needed to guide social conversations about art, to prevent them from devolving into mere speculation. We also learned that correctly navigating a museum’s exhibits is an important aspect of the museum experience, and that different genres of art should be treated differently (some art is consumed together, as an exhibit, others individually). In addition, information can enhance the museum experience, but too much information can also distract the viewer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;design-research-themes&quot;&gt;Design Research Themes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From our contextual inquiries, we:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Confirmed that learning is the ultimate goal for art museum-goers&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Discovered these learning experiences are unique to the individual&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Resources that support learning about art must be customizable&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Discussion about art is critical to the individual experience of art&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Art discussion may need guidance from scholars to prevent mere speculation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learning as the primary goal of museum-goers reinforces the necessity of a more accessible resource, which was our initial intuition. Context and background information on art presented in colloquial terms is integral to this learning process. Our inquiries revealed that current museum resources do not communicate enough context about art. The information gap is often due to the limited physical space in museums. Information is disseminated to users in the form of placards, wall text, and pamphlets, which are often not used by visitors. This confirms the motivation for our design solution. In addition, visiting museums is a social experience, and discussion is a crucial part in gaining new knowledge in an informal way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On a high level, we also uncovered the nature of the learning experience when it comes to art. Because we are dealing with the subjective experience of enjoying art, the entire journey of art learning at museums must also accommodate a range of individual experiences. This personalization must be considered at all points of the learning experience, starting with the initial art background and interest level of the users to how and what they aim to learn. We learned that people enjoy relating art back to their own lives, so they must be able to practice individuality when engaging with any kind of art. In wanting to maintain their autonomy, they may explicitly choose not to learn too much background information about an art piece, and may simply want to engage with it themselves. Users must be able to make this choice for themselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Social discussion plays a large part in this; it allows users to participate in an informal discussion about art that allows them to gain new knowledge, and yet it still allows them to express their individually. An example of this is when we noticed museum-goers asking museum staff specific questions about art pieces. This was one avenue through which they were able to tailor the amount of background knowledge they wanted to their needs. However, scholarly input, on a colloquial and discussion-based level, may still be necessary and provide valuable insight about the true nature of artworks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/affinity-diagram.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Affinity Diagram&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Affinity Diagram&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through affinity diagramming, we were able to identify these high-level themes, as shown by the pink and purple post-its in the diagram above. By grouping similar statements from our interviewees together, we were able to pinpoint commonalities in the learning experience in art museums. For example, we noticed that the Art History professor stated that placards are informative but can be distracting, and actually both students noted that too much background information can actually take away from their appreciation of an artwork. To us, this meant that users would want to customize and tailor their learning to fit their needs. We used this kind of process to move from specific statements by specific users to general statements about groups of users throughout the construction of our affinity diagram.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry></feed>