<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.6.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-05-04T14:24:44-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/</id><title type="html">CSCI376 Project: Art for All</title><subtitle>Collaborative platform for artistic engagement</subtitle><author><name>Art for All</name></author><entry><title type="html">Understanding To Make Final Report</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/understanding-to-make-final-report/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Understanding To Make Final Report" /><published>2018-04-30T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-04-30T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/understanding-to-make-final-report</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/understanding-to-make-final-report/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;project&quot;&gt;Project&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Art for All: An interactive and educational platform for public engagement at art museums&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;team-members&quot;&gt;Team Members&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Joyce Wang, Stephanie Liu, and Cliff Makanda. We have decided to all serve as generalists on the team, to get a chance to try out all of the roles and act as equal team members.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;problem-and-solution-overview&quot;&gt;Problem and Solution Overview&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Art museums have long been a primary resource for learning about and experiencing art. Unfortunately, art can often feel intimidatingly inaccessible for the general public. For regular people, who aren’t academics or involved in the “art world,” art can feel elusive, out-of-touch, or even perhaps just confusing. Without a formal introduction to art, which is generally only available to the privileged, it becomes difficult to glean much insight from abstract and unfamiliar artworks. This problem stems from both the little information museums provide about artworks as well as the lack of informal resources available for engaging in conversations about art. Art for All intends to overcome these hurdles by providing a simple and easy-to-use framework for finding background information about artworks and artists, and allowing users to engage in informal discussions about specific artworks online. In this way, users from a diverse set of backgrounds can come together to discuss their varied interpretations of art to get a better understanding of how art can impact their lives. In addition, background information will be readily accessible and easy to understand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;initial-paper-prototype&quot;&gt;Initial Paper Prototype&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This &lt;a href=&quot;../paper-prototype&quot;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; shows an overview of the initial paper prototype we constructed, that would be used for later testing. It also demonstrates how the prototype would be used to carry out each of our two main tasks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;testing-process&quot;&gt;Testing Process&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This &lt;a href=&quot;../testing-process&quot;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; outlines the heuristic evaluations and usability tests we conducted with our initial paper prototype in order to refine and iterate on our design. It also includes revisions we made to our testing format and what we learned from the initial tests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;testing-results&quot;&gt;Testing Results&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This &lt;a href=&quot;../testing-results&quot;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; details the key results we learned from each of our tests, and the subsequent revisions we made to our paper prototype.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;final-paper-prototype&quot;&gt;Final Paper Prototype&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After receiving feedback from the heuristic evaluations and usability tests, we constructed a new final paper prototype that can be found &lt;a href=&quot;../final-paper-prototype&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. The post outlines all the changes made from critiques, as well as walkthroughs of how the final paper prototype would be used in each of our two key tasks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;digital-mockup&quot;&gt;Digital Mockup&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We used Sketch and InVision to create our digital mockup. This &lt;a href=&quot;../final-digital-mock-up&quot;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; presents an overview of our design as well as walkthroughs using the design for each of our two main tasks. It also includes any revisions we made moving from paper to digital, as well as those we made after receiving feedback on our initial digital mockup.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;discussion&quot;&gt;Discussion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We learned a lot about the process of iterative design, and found the techniques really helpful in refining our design. We didn’t realize how many issues could come up, even with the limited functionality we used in our paper prototype. The heuristic evaluations provided a solid foundation for us to go off of, and then the usability tests provided more subjective tweaks that enhanced the design in different ways. We also refined the process of our usability tests as we learned about what aspects of the tests we wanted to change. Our primary tasks did not actually change much as a result of the usability tests, probably because they were so straight forward to begin with. However, our design certainly changed a lot as we received feedback and critiques. We probably did just about the right number of iterations necessary for our limited design scope. We certainly could have done more, and would have tweaked the design in helpful ways, but the marginal benefits would have likely started tapering off eventually. That being said, the design would not be nearly as good as it is now had it not been for the iterative design approach. We quickly realized that we were assuming background knowledge that our users might not have when we created our inital paper prototype, and had to refine our design to be more explicit about its functionality. The launch page was an example of a key revision we needed to make in order to allow the user to build an efficient “mental model” of the scope of the app. We also realized that we built the initial paper prototype in one direction (click these buttons to get here), but often forgot about back buttons and “emergency exits” that we had to add in later. These changes made our app much more intuitive and easy to use for all of our users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;appendix&quot;&gt;Appendix&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;instructions-for-usability-tests&quot;&gt;Instructions for Usability Tests&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below are the instructions we read out loud and printed for our usability testing participants to refer to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This is a study about an educational and social platform for learning about artworks in museums and discussing the art with others. Our goal is to make the app as appealing, usable, and intuitive as possible. Your input and observations will help us refine our design.&lt;br /&gt;
We will provide a “paper prototype” for you to use as you carry about the main tasks that we are designing for. Another team member will be writing notes as you carry out these tasks. Feel free to ask us questions as you carry out the tasks, but know that we may not always be able to answer right away because we won’t be there for our future users. Please try to talk aloud as you move through the tasks, so we can understand what’s going on in your head.&lt;br /&gt;
All of the information we collect from this study will be anonymized after, and we will not videotape or record you.&lt;br /&gt;
Remember that we are testing the product, not you! Don’t worry if you don’t understand something or get confused. Those insights will help us understand where our design has failed and where we may need to make the design more clear.&lt;br /&gt;
Know that you can quit at any time. Your participation is valuable to us, but is entire voluntary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;task-descriptions-for-usability-tests&quot;&gt;Task Descriptions for Usability Tests&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After our first usability test, we decided to print out task descriptions to hand out to participants. They would read the task description out loud before attempting to carry out the task with the paper prototype. We printed out the task descriptions on separate sheets of paper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;task-1-finding-background-information&quot;&gt;Task 1: Finding Background Information&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;You are in a museum looking at different artworks. You come across a piece you’d like to learn more about, and you see a QR code on the placard next to the piece. You’re specifically interested in finding out what the artist’s inspiration was when creating this piece. Please try to find this information by looking it up using the app.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;task-2-discussing-art-with-others&quot;&gt;Task 2: Discussing Art with Others&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Now that you have found the inspiration for this piece, you might want to discuss what the piece means to you with others. Please try and add to the discussion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;task-25-catching-up-with-your-discussions&quot;&gt;Task 2.5: Catching Up with Your Discussions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;After leaving the museum, you get a notification on your phone that someone has replied to your comment. Starting from the main screen, try to navigate back to the comment you made to see what their response was.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Testing Results and Revisions</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/testing-results/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Testing Results and Revisions" /><published>2018-04-30T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-04-30T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/testing-results</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/testing-results/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;heuristic-evaluations&quot;&gt;Heuristic Evaluations&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The heuristic evaluations demonstrated the following major problems and consequent revisions:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;1-unclear-initial-search-page&quot;&gt;1. Unclear initial search page&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;before&quot;&gt;Before:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We received feedback that a primary function of our application, which allows the user to scan a QR code using the mobile phone’s camera, was not clear. The camera icon was too close to the search bar, and the camera did not provide any indication that it would be used to scan QR codes. This issue violates the visibility of system heuristic, and received a severity rating of 3.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper-prototype-search.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 50%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Search menu&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;after&quot;&gt;After:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To clarify the two search options and provide more context on functionality, we labelled and separated the two components in a large button menu.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/pp-cam-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 50%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Two separated components with clear labeling&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;2-missing-back-buttons&quot;&gt;2. Missing back button(s)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;before-1&quot;&gt;Before:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our evaluators pointed out that after navigating to inspiration, it was unclear how to get back to the main about section. They felt stuck. This violated the User Control and Freedom heuristic, and received a severity rating of 1.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper-prototype-inspo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 50%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Inspiration section of &quot;Learn more&quot; &lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;after-1&quot;&gt;After:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Revision: A back button was added.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/pp-about-inspo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 50%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Back button added&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;3-unnecessary-screen-components&quot;&gt;3. Unnecessary screen components&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;before-2&quot;&gt;Before:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Always having the bottom toolbar felt redundant to evaluators in certain contexts. This added clutter and made the design difficult to navigate. This violated the Aesthetics and Minimalist Design heuristic, and received a severity rating of 2.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper-prototype-cam.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;About&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 50%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Camera screen&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper-prototype-discuss.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Learn More&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 50%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Discussion screen&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;after-2&quot;&gt;After:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Revision: The design should only provide information that is needed and is helpful to the user. We decided to drop the bottom bar wherever it was easy for the user to still go back one page and find the bottom bar easily should they need it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/pp-cam-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;About&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 50%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Camera screen removes toolbar&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/pp-discuss.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Learn More&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 50%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Discussion screen removes toolbar&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;usability-testing-results&quot;&gt;Usability Testing Results&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We encountered the following critical incidents from our usability tests, broken down by each usability test in order:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;results-from-test-1&quot;&gt;Results from Test 1&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;1-re-organizing-the-about-more-and-learn-more-content&quot;&gt;1. Re-organizing the “About More” and “Learn More” content&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;before-3&quot;&gt;Before:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While trying to navigate to a page that contained the inspiration for an artwork, we realized that it wasn’t clear to a general user whether the inspiration information should be under “about” or “learn more.” This led us to believe we may want to put more information about the inspiration and context under the “about” tab, and leave very in-depth understanding to the “learn more” section (e.g. further information about the artist and the history of the movement).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper-prototype-about.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;About&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 50%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;About screen under artwork profile&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper-prototype-learnmore.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Learn More&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 50%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Learn More screen under artwork profile&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;after-3&quot;&gt;After:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Revision: The “About” page was modified to contain information that used to be in the “Learn More” section, and the “Learn More” section was modified to be a series of very in-depth information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/pp-about.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 50%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;New About Page&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/pp-learn-more.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 50%;\
&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;New Learn More Page&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;2-qr-code-scanner&quot;&gt;2. QR code scanner&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;before-4&quot;&gt;Before:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While trying to “fake” taking a scan of the QR code, our user noted that he didn’t really know where to put the QR code, and that it would be nice to have a box on the camera screen so the user knows exactly where to put it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper-prototype-qrscan.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;QR Scanner&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 50%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;QR Scanner&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;after-4&quot;&gt;After:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Revision: Adding a box/grid layout to indicate where the QR code should be captured.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/pp-cam-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;About&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 50%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;QR code screen indicates placementr&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;3-discussion&quot;&gt;3. Discussion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper-prototype-discussion-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Discussion&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Discussion&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;incident&quot;&gt;Incident:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was a positive incident; our user was quickly and easily able to locate the “discussion” section and understand the gist of the interface and how it would operate. This is likely because discussions like this exist in similar formats on other platforms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;results-from-test-2&quot;&gt;Results from Test 2&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;1-favoriting-artworks&quot;&gt;1. Favoriting artworks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;before-5&quot;&gt;Before:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Favoriting and adding artworks to the user’s profile was not readily apparent. Although participant 2 was able to discover this feature after exploring the application and browsing his user profile, the discovery was only in hindsight after he had already left the artwork profile screen. Because favoriting artworks is one of our six primary tasks and the main feature of the user profile, this feature needed to be made more obvious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/favorite_old.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Old Favorite&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 50%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Old favorite button&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;after-5&quot;&gt;After:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Revision:  Our solution was to change the favorite button into a more visible button right underneath the work’s title. We also added some more explicit text to make this functionality even more obvious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/favorite_new.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;New Favorite&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 50%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;New favorite button&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;2-qr-code-search-tutorial&quot;&gt;2. QR Code Search Tutorial&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;before-6&quot;&gt;Before:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both participants two and three did not understand the capability to scan QR codes, which was another negative incident. However, once this feature of being able to scan the QR codes displayed on artwork placards was explained to them, both preferred to use this over the text search.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/tutorial_old.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Old Tutorial&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 50%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Old initial search screen&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;after-6&quot;&gt;After:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Revision: To solve this problem of not effectively communicating the ability to use QR codes to look up artworks, upon launching the “Search” mode for the first time, a one-time tutorial overlay page outlines the QR code look-up process for the user.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/tutorial_new.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;New Tutorial&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 50%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;New initial search screen&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;results-from-test-3&quot;&gt;Results from Test 3&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;1-confusing-syntax&quot;&gt;1. Confusing syntax&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;before-7&quot;&gt;Before:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some of the syntax employed resulted in negative incidents, as they did not successfully translate their ascribed functionality. In particular, on the search page, participant 3 didn’t understand the difference between being in the “Search” mode and the button option to “Search.” Additionally, she did not recognize that the “Threads” section of the User Profile would display the threads she participated in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/search_old.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Old Search&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 50%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Old search syntax&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/threads_old.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Old Thread&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 50%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Old thread syntax&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;after-7&quot;&gt;After:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Revision: Words were changed to better suit the user’s vocabulary and increase the usability of these key interactions. We changed the text for searching by text to “Text Search” instead of just “Search,” and changed the “Threads” tab to say “Your Threads”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/search_new.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;New Search&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 50%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;New search syntax&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/threads_new.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;New Thread&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 50%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;New thread syntax&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;2-launch-screen&quot;&gt;2. Launch screen&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;before-8&quot;&gt;Before:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Upon opening the application and being shown the initial screen for the “Search mode,” the user went to the “Museum Profile” for the purposes of initially exploring the application. This incident was negative, as the order of interaction was not intuitive to our test users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;after-8&quot;&gt;After:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Revision: A launch screen was added to be an initial museum profile screen. It communicates that the app is museum-specific and clearly defines what the purpose of the “museum” tab is. The museum profile orients the user toward accomplishing the task of searching for individual art pieces.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/ppf_homepage.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;homepage&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 50%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Launch screen&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;summary--key-revisions&quot;&gt;Summary &amp;amp; Key Revisions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the key revisions we made was the search functionality. First, we added in clear and large buttons to delineate the difference between the text search and the QR search. Then we added more explicit text so that the users could distinguish between the kinds of search and understand why they were different. Lastly, we added in a one-time tutorial of how the QR search functionality would work. All of these changes helped make the search function much clearer and improve the usability. Since searching for the artwork to pull up its artwork profile is a key functionality of our design, this was very important to us to change. Another key revision was changing how the “About” and “Learn More” pages were divided, and we found that after the first usability test, we needed to make this distinction more intuitive. We decided to modify what kinds of information would be located under each tab. In our second and third usability tests, we noticed that this distinction was a lot more clear to our users, and they had no problem finding what they needed with this modification. Thus, we found this change to be incredibly important for our design and usability. Obviously, since finding background information is a key task we are trying to support, making it as easy as possible for the user to find the background information they are explicitly looking for is important to us. Lastly, adding the launch page to be the museum profile was a key revision for us, because it helps orient the user and helps her understand what the other tabs are for. We didn’t realize that the “Museum Profile” tab might be confusing to the user if they are not brought there first, so this was another key revision. It helps the user build a correct “mental model” of how the app works.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Testing Process</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/testing-process/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Testing Process" /><published>2018-04-30T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-04-30T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/testing-process</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/testing-process/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;method-overview-and-refinements&quot;&gt;Method Overview and Refinements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We conducted two types of tests: heuristics evaluations and usability tests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The heuristic evaluations were carried out according to Nielsen’s heuristics sheet, and we had two different groups evaluate our design. The evaluators identified potential issues with our design, noted the heuristics violated, and assigned a severity score to each issue. For detailed images of the evaluator’s comments, refer to the &lt;a href=&quot;../heuristic-evaluations&quot;&gt;Heuristic Evaluations page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For our usability tests, we followed the test protocol outlined in Kathleen Gomoll’s, “Some Techniques for Observing Users,” starting with a brief explanation of the app, and the format and rules for the usability test. The exact wording and specifications we used can be found in the Appendix of our &lt;a href=&quot;../understanding-to-make-final-report&quot;&gt;final report&lt;/a&gt;.  We then explained each of our two main tasks in a scenario format, and asked the user to carry out the tasks. For the first usability test, Stephanie was the facilitator, and Joyce took notes. After our first usability test, we found that by not actually writing down the tasks and giving them to our participant to refer to, the conversation often derailed into other topics that did not pertain to the task. In our subsequent tests, we then refined our approach by printing out the tasks for our participants, and found that it helped the test stay focused. In addition, we updated our pre-test briefings to be more specific about the goals of the usability test. Cliff conducted the second test, and Joyce took notes. We found that the second test was in fact much more streamlined, and the printed out tasks were very helpful in making the process more explicit. The last test was conducted by Joyce while Stephanie took notes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;participants&quot;&gt;Participants&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our first usability test was conducted with a Williams College senior, in a study room in Sawyer Library. We chose to start with him because he sits in the upper-end in terms of his art education and background. He is not an art history major but has taken four art history classes at Williams and has a deep appreciation for art. We explained each of our two main tasks in a scenario format and asked him to carry out those tasks while explaining his thought process and asking questions (even if we couldn’t answer them).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second usability test participant was with a Williams College junior. We chose him because he had little background in art education, and only visited museums very infrequently. The test was again conducted in Sawyer Library. We started by laying out written brief scenarios of being in the museum and approaching a painting. Both the second and third usability tests differed from the first test in that the participants were provided with written scenarios and were asked to read them out loud and refer to them as they carried out the two tasks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The last usability test participant was with a Williams College senior. She has taken a few art history courses for fun, but does not have a strong background in art. She also expressed a particular interest in this kind of app, because she often finds herself not understanding the art she sees at museums. The test was also conducted in Sawyer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our heuristics evaluations were carried out as part of an in-class exercise with two different groups. Joyce and Stephanie facilitated the first evaluation which was performed by Karl. Cliff facilitated the last evaluation which was performed by Alyssa and Lester. The evaluators were familiar with our project and with Jakob Nielsen’s heuristic principles. The groups simulated first time users, asked questions, noted any heuristics broken, and indicated the severities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;summary&quot;&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Conducting usability tests and heuristic evaluations provided helpful insight into the problems and challenges that might be encountered by users using our app for the first time. Asking the usability test participants to read the tasks out loud, talk us through their actions, and ask questions, helped us understand their thought process while using the app. Several issues were identified through the usability test and heuristic evaluations. The usability tests highlighted that some of our design choices needed to be better refined to be clearly understood by the users. Heuristic evaluations provided a systematic way to evaluate our app design. Our use of different groups with different levels of experience for our use cases made our testing process effective.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Final Paper Prototype</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/final-paper-prototype/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Final Paper Prototype" /><published>2018-04-29T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-04-29T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/final-paper-prototype</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/final-paper-prototype/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;overview-of-final-paper-prototype&quot;&gt;Overview of Final Paper Prototype&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/ppf_all.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Final Paper Prototype&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our final paper prototype integrates the changes we made from the feedback we received in our heuristic evaluations and usability tests. We added the “Favorite” text to the button users use to favorite pieces because some users found the simple heart image ambiguous. We changed the tab for “Threads” on the user profile to “Your Threads,” also to make the functionality less ambiguous. We added a one-time tutorial to the beginning of the QR search function to make it more clear, and added an outline on the camera screen to indicate where the QR code should go. We also added a new search screen so users could understand the difference between a QR search and a text search. We also added back buttons where there weren’t ones before, and removed the bottom bar of tabs where it wasn’t necessary. The use of the final paper prototype in our two tasks is outlined below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;task-1-finding-background-information-about-artworks&quot;&gt;Task 1: Finding background information about artworks&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/ppf_searchmenu.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;User begins in search menu&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/ppf_qrinstruct.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;User chooses QR code scan, and is presented with a one-time tutorial on how to use the QR code scanning function&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/ppf_cam.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;User clicks anywhere on the screen to get to the camera&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/ppf_qrsearch.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;User scans QR code&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/ppf_about.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;App scans QR and navigates to artwork profile, beginning in About section&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/ppf_inspo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;User clicks on inspiration&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/ppf_learnmore.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;User clicks on Learn More&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;task-2-discussing-art-with-others&quot;&gt;Task 2: Discussing art with others&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/ppf_about.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;User begins on front page of artwork’s profile&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/ppf_discuss.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;User clicks on Discussion&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/ppf_typediscuss.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;User clicks on the text field and types a comment&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/ppf_discussposted.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;User submits comment, and it shows up at the top of the comments section&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;some-time-later-user-can-check-up-on-her-threads-and-see-if-anyone-has-responded-to-her-comments&quot;&gt;Some time later, user can check up on her threads and see if anyone has responded to her comments&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/ppf_faves.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;User navigates to user profile&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/ppf_yourthreads.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;User clicks on “Your Threads,” and can check up on old threads from there.&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Digital Mock-Up</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/final-digital-mock-up/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Digital Mock-Up" /><published>2018-04-29T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-04-29T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/final-digital-mock-up</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/final-digital-mock-up/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;overview-of-digital-mock-up&quot;&gt;Overview of Digital Mock-Up&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/digf-all.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Final Digital Mock-Up&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;task-1-learning-background-information-about-artworks&quot;&gt;Task 1: Learning Background Information about Artworks&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/digf-qr.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;From the launch page, the user can choose the &quot;Search&quot; tab in the bottom navigation bar. This pulls up the choice between a QR search and a Text Search. If the user chooses the QR search function, then the user will be presented with a one-time tutorial on how to use this functionality. A camera is then presented for the user to scan the appropriate QR code.&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/digf-search.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Alternatively, the user may choose to search by text. In this case, a list of search results will load continuously as the user types in key search words. &lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/digf-aboutlearnmore.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Once the user finds the artwork she is looking for, she may click on the artwork to take her to the artwork profile. From the artwork profile, the user can tab between &quot;About&quot; and &quot;Learn More,&quot; and investigate the information under each. Shown here is the &quot;Analysis&quot; portion of the &quot;About&quot; page.&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;task-2-participating-in-discussions-about-art-with-other-users&quot;&gt;Task 2: Participating in Discussions about Art with Other Users&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/digf-discuss.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;The artwork profile also contains a &quot;Discussion&quot; tab. The user can read through others' comments, reply to threads, or start new threads. There are different labels signifying which users have a scholarly background in art. In this scenario, the user decides to write a new comment to join the discussion.&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/digf-yourthreads.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;When the user navigates to the user profile, he can see all the threads he has notifications in. In this case, someone has responded to his previous comment. The user can then click on that notification, and will be taken to the discussion section of the artwork. The user can then choose to respond to that new comment. &lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;revisions&quot;&gt;Revisions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We actually found that we were able to keep many of the components of our paper prototype the same when moving to a digital mock-up. One change that stands out is that we decided to get rid of icons in the discussion sections. Since mobile platforms have so little space to begin with, we decided it wasn’t worth including icons, and they wouldn’t add much to the discussion experience. We also modified the QR code scanning button to be a picture of a QR code rather than a camera, as we thought that might be more indicative of its use. After we reviewed the critiques we received, we increased the size of the tabs to at least 40px for “Full Artist Biography,” “Analysis,” “Context,” etc, increased the size of buttons to at least 40px for “Favorite” and “Post,” and increased the text sizes across the website to at least 12px.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;citations&quot;&gt;Citations&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;artwork-nebraska&quot;&gt;Artwork (Nebraska):&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Barbara Takenaga “Nebraska” image can be found &lt;a href=&quot;http://massmoca.org/13035-2/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;
All text included in the subsequent sections about “Nebraska” were also borrowed from that MASS MoCA website above.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;user-profile-images&quot;&gt;User Profile Images:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jackson Pollock’s “The Deep” can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jackson-pollock.org/the-deep.jsp&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;
Jackson Pollock’s “Number One” can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jackson-pollock.org/number-1.jsp&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;
Picasso’s “Girl before a Mirror” can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.moma.org/calendar/exhibitions/283&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;
Barbara Takenaga’s “Wheel (Nimbus)” can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.printed-editions.com/art-print/barbara-takenaga-wheel-nimbus-49561&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;
The user png can be found &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.stickpng.com/img/icons-logos-emojis/users/simple-user-icon&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;
(All other icons were created by hand on the Sketch design app).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;search-images&quot;&gt;Search Images:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;QR Code image can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/QR_code&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;launch-screen&quot;&gt;Launch Screen:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MASS MoCA map can be found &lt;a href=&quot;http://solidsound.wpengine.netdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/SSF17Map.jpg&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Heuristic Evaluations</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/heuristic-evaluations/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Heuristic Evaluations" /><published>2018-04-09T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-04-09T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/heuristic-evaluations</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/heuristic-evaluations/">&lt;p&gt;Stephanie and Joyce facilitated an heuristic evaluation performed by Karl on our paper prototype (and vice versa for Pin’s prototype). His full evaluation is below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/heuristic-karl-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Karl&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Karl's written evaluation&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cliff facilitated an evaluation performed by Alyssa and Lester (and vice versa for Pin’s prototype). Their full evaluations are below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/heuristic-alyssa-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Alyssa&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Alyssa's written evaluation&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/heuristic-lester-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lester&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Lester's written evaluation&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An overview image of the paper prototype we used for evaluation is also shown below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper_prototyping_overview.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Overview&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Components of paper prototype&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To see the evaluations we performed on Pin’s paper prototype, please refer to Pin’s project page.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Initial Paper Prototype</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/paper-prototype/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Initial Paper Prototype" /><published>2018-04-04T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-04-04T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/paper-prototype</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/paper-prototype/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;design&quot;&gt;Design&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Art for All is a mobile application that allows users to learn more about the art pieces users see in museums&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tasks&quot;&gt;Tasks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Learn more context and background information to better understand the meaning behind artworks&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Discuss artwork with others in order to further engage with the pieces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;overview-of-initial-paper-prototype&quot;&gt;Overview of Initial Paper Prototype&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;../assets/images/paper_prototyping_overview.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper_prototyping_overview.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Components of paper prototype&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The application has three primary modes: the museum profile, search, and user profile. The yellow highlighted box indicates which mode the user is in. Initially opening the application brings the user to the default Search mode page, as shown in Screen 1.1. From this page, users have the option to choose between either a text search, as shown in Screens 1.2, 1.3, or a QR code search, as shown in Screens 1.4, 1.5, 1.6 Both lead to a results page, in Screen 1.7, where the desired artwork can be chosen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;../assets/images/paper_prototyping_ search.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper_prototyping_ search.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Searching artwork&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clicking on the artwork opens a nested artwork profile page with “About” (Screen 2.1), “Learn More,” and “Discussion” tabs that the user can toggle between to support the first task of discovering more context about artworks. The “Learn More” tab (Screen 2.3) contains links to further background information, including “Context,” “Inspiration,” “History,” and “Genre” that can be explored, as shown in Screen 2.5.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;../assets/images/paper_prototyping_ art_profile_1.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper_prototyping_ art_profile_1.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Artwork Profile&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;../assets/images/paper_prototyping_ art_profile_2.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper_prototyping_ art_profile_2.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Artwork Profile (cont.)&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The “Discussion” tab (Screen 2.7) supports the task of discussing art with others. In this tab, users can post and reply to other users’ comments about this artwork, as shown in Screens 2.7-12 above.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;../assets/images/paper_prototyping_ user_profile.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper_prototyping_ user_profile.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;User Profile&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clicking on the User Profile mode displays the initial Screen 3.1. The user profile displays a header containing a user profile picture, name, and bio. The body of the page consist of “Favorites” and “Threads” tabs. The “Favorites” tab displays favorited artworks. Clicking on any of these artworks, in Screen 3.2, brings the user to a nested art profile page, in Screen 3.3. The “Threads” tab (Screen 3.5) displays a list of discussions the user has participated in and highlights those with unread replies. Clicking on any of these comments, in Screen 3.6, opens the corresponding nested discussion page, as shown in Screen 3.7.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Looking to Understand Final Report</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/looking-to-understand-final-report/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Looking to Understand Final Report" /><published>2018-04-04T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-04-04T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/looking-to-understand-final-report</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/looking-to-understand-final-report/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;project&quot;&gt;Project&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Art for All: An interactive and educational platform for public engagement at art museums&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;team-members-all-generalists&quot;&gt;Team Members (all generalists):&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cliff Makanda, Stephanie Liu, Joyce Wang&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;problem-and-solution-overview&quot;&gt;Problem and Solution Overview:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Art museums have long been a primary resource for learning about and experiencing art. Unfortunately, art can often feel intimidatingly inaccessible for the general public. For regular people, who aren’t academics or involved in the “art world,” art can feel elusive, out-of-touch, or even perhaps just confusing. Without a formal introduction to art, which is generally only available to the privileged, it becomes difficult to glean much insight from abstract and unfamiliar artworks. This problem stems from both the little information museums provide about artworks as well as the lack of informal resources available for engaging in conversations about art. Art for All intends to overcome these hurdles by providing a simple and easy-to-use framework for finding background information about artworks and artists, and allowing users to engage in informal discussions about specific artworks online. In this way, users from a diverse set of backgrounds can come together to discuss their varied interpretations of art to get a better understanding of how art can impact their lives. In addition, background information will be readily accessible and easy to understand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;design-research-goals-stakeholders-and-participants&quot;&gt;Design Research: Goals, Stakeholders, and Participants&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This &lt;a href=&quot;../design-research-goals-stakeholders-and-participants&quot;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; provides information about the methods and process we used for gathering design research through interviews and contextual inquiries, as well as detailed accounts of the participants, their backgrounds, and the environments in which they were interviewed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;design-research-results-and-themes&quot;&gt;Design Research: Results and Themes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This &lt;a href=&quot;../design-research-results-and-themes&quot;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; provides an overview of the key results and themes from our design research, as found through affinity diagramming. The emergence of these key themes allowed us to guide our design to specifically tailor user needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;task-analysis&quot;&gt;Task Analysis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This &lt;a href=&quot;../task-analysis&quot;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; details our answers to specific task analysis questions, and allows us to set the scope of our design as it relates to the users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;proposed-design-sketches-3x4&quot;&gt;Proposed Design Sketches (“3x4”)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This &lt;a href=&quot;../Proposed-Design-Sketches-3-x-4&quot;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; presents three different potential design choices, and details the specific tasks they are designed to support. An updated design is presented at the end, with an explanation for why that specific design was ultimately chosen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;written-scenarios-1x2&quot;&gt;Written Scenarios (“1x2”)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This &lt;a href=&quot;../Written-Scenarios-1-x-2&quot;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; details the two selected tasks we chose to support in our final design, and written scenarios for each task that correspond to the storyboards as presented in the next section.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;storyboards&quot;&gt;Storyboards&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This &lt;a href=&quot;../Storyboards&quot;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; presents the two storyboards that correspond to our selected tasks.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Storyboards</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Storyboards/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Storyboards" /><published>2018-03-12T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-03-12T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Storyboards</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Storyboards/">&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/storyboard-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Storyboard 1&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Storyboard 1: Finding background information task &lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/storyboard-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Storyboard 2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Storyboard 2: Participating in online discussions about art task&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Written Scenarios (“1x2”)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Written-Scenarios-1-x-2/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Written Scenarios (“1x2”)" /><published>2018-03-11T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-03-11T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Written-Scenarios-1-x-2</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Written-Scenarios-1-x-2/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;selected-supported-tasks&quot;&gt;Selected Supported Tasks&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our two selected tasks are finding background information about an artwork, and engaging in online discussions focused on specific artworks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finding background information is an activity that is central to the museum experience. We found during our contextual inquiries that all of the people we talked to came to the museum to learn about art, although some emphasized different aspects of that learning. In either case, we definitely wanted to highlight this learning aspect in our app.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the discussion side, we mostly interviewed people who were already in groups, and we noticed how they enjoyed talking to each other about the art as they went along. The discussion task will thus allow for a wider conversation to take place with a more diverse set of people. In addition, people who find themselves visiting a museum alone will still get to discuss their experience with others. Art is a social experience. A museum-goer should not only be able to communicate with an artwork but also with other museum-goers. This allows for cross pollination of ideas and different interpretations of art.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;scenarios&quot;&gt;Scenarios&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;scenario-1-finding-background-information&quot;&gt;Scenario 1: Finding background information&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ben is visiting his local art museum and comes across a piece that really strikes him. He wants to know more, so he pulls up the Art for All app and navigates to the search tab. He clicks on the camera button and scans a picture of the QR code on the artworks’ panel. The app pulls up the artworks’ profile, and he clicks on the Learn More tab. He wants to learn about the inspiration for the piece, so he clicks on the Inspiration section and reads about the artists’ inspiration for the work. When he has read as much info as he’d like to know, he closes the app and moves on to investigate more in the museum. See &lt;a href=&quot;../Storyboards&quot;&gt;Storyboard 1&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;scenario-2-discussing-art&quot;&gt;Scenario 2: Discussing Art&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bob has recently visited a museum and become entranced with a Jackson Pollock work. He is waiting for the bus, and thinks back to this piece. He decides he wants to discuss this particular artwork with others, so he pulls up the Art for All app and navigates to the discussion section under this artwork profile page. He asks some probing questions, and finds that another student, Sarah, is also online at the same time and wants to talk about this particular work. They discuss their interpretations, and in the end Bob feels like he has a better understanding of the artwork. See &lt;a href=&quot;../Storyboards&quot;&gt;Storyboard 2&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry></feed>