<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.6.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-04-19T00:59:03-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/</id><title type="html">CSCI376 Project: Art for All</title><subtitle>Collaborative platform for artistic engagement</subtitle><author><name>Art for All</name></author><entry><title type="html">Digital Mock-Up</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/digital-mock-up/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Digital Mock-Up" /><published>2018-04-19T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-04-19T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/digital-mock-up</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/digital-mock-up/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;overview-of-digital-mock-up&quot;&gt;Overview of Digital Mock-Up&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/mockup-overview.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Digital Mock-Up&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/mockup-launch.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Launch screen that provides information about the museum and the museum map to navigate exhibits.&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;task-1-learning-background-information-about-artworks&quot;&gt;Task 1: Learning Background Information about Artworks&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/mockup-qr.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;From the launch page, the user can choose the &quot;Search&quot; tab in the bottom navigation bar. This pulls up the choice between a QR search and a Text Search. If the user chooses the QR search function, then the user will be presented with a one-time tutorial on how to use this functionality. A camera is then presented for the user to scan the appropriate QR code.&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/mockup-text-search.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Alternatively, the user may choose to search by text. In this case, a list of search results will load continuously as the user types in key search words. &lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/mockup-learn.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Once the user finds the artwork she is looking for, she may click on the artwork to take her to the artwork profile. From the artwork profile, the user can tab between &quot;About&quot; and &quot;Learn More,&quot; and investigate the information under each. Shown here is the &quot;Analysis&quot; portion of the &quot;About&quot; page.&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;task-2-participating-in-discussions-about-art-with-other-users&quot;&gt;Task 2: Participating in Discussions about Art with Other Users&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/mockup-discuss.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;The artwork profile also contains a &quot;Discussion&quot; tab. The user can read through others' comments, reply to threads, or start new threads. There are different labels signifying which users have a scholarly background in art. In this scenario, the user decides to write a new comment to join the discussion.&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/mockup-discuss.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;When the user navigates to the user profile, he can see all the threads he has notifications in. In this case, someone has responded to his previous comment. The user can then click on that notification, and will be taken to the discussion section of the artwork. The user can then choose to respond to that new comment. &lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Usability Testing Review</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/usability-testing-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Usability Testing Review" /><published>2018-04-15T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-04-15T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/usability-testing-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/usability-testing-review/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;usability-test-overviews&quot;&gt;Usability Test Overviews&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;usability-test-1&quot;&gt;Usability Test #1&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We conducted the first usability test with a senior at Williams, in a study room in Sawyer Library. We chose to start with him because he is not an art history major but has taken four art history classes at Williams and has a deep appreciation for art, so he sits in the middle in terms of art education. We followed the test protocol outlined in Kathleen Gomoll’s “Some Techniques for Observing Users,” starting with a brief explanation of the app and the format and rules for the usability test. (We followed the same protocol for the following two usability tests as well). We explained each of our two main tasks in a scenario format for the user, and asked him to carry out those tasks while explaining his thought process and asking questions (even if we couldn’t answer them). Stephanie facilitated the usability test, and Joyce took notes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;usability-test-2&quot;&gt;Usability Test #2&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our second usability test participant was a junior at Williams. We chose him because he is familiar with the purpose of the app and its use case. We started the tests by laying out brief scenarios on paper of being in the museum and approaching a painting. We modified this and the following test compared to the first test by writing these scenarios down on paper and giving them to our participant to read out loud and refer to throughout the test. This test was conducted in Sawyer Library, a quiet space. Cliff conducted the test, and Joyce took notes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;usability-test-3&quot;&gt;Usability Test #3&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our third usability test participant was a female senior at Williams. We chose her because she expressed interest in the app, as she does find herself not understanding some of the pieces she sees in art museums. She has taken a few art history courses and so is not unfamiliar with the subject matter. Because she did not know anything about the project, we prefaced the test by giving her the same scenario as above and explaining that the app is meant to help people learn more about art pieces. The test was also conducted in Sawyer. Joyce conducted the test, and Stephanie took notes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;critical-incidents-and-revisions&quot;&gt;Critical Incidents and Revisions&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;about-vs-learn-more&quot;&gt;“About” vs “Learn More”&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper-prototype-about.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;About&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;About screen under artwork profile&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper-prototype-learnmore.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Learn More&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Learn More screen under artwork profile&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incident:&lt;/strong&gt; While trying to navigate to a page that contained the inspiration for an artwork, we realized that it wasn’t clear to a general user whether the inspiration information should be under “about” or “learn more.” This led us to believe we may want to put more information about the inspiration and context under the “about” tab, and leave very in-depth understanding to the “learn more” section (e.g. further information about the artist and the history of the movement).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Severity Level:&lt;/strong&gt; 3 (This is one of the main tasks our app is trying to support).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Revision:&lt;/strong&gt; Modifying the “Learn More” section to be a series of very in-depth information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/pp-about.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;New About Page&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/pp-learn-more.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;\
&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;New Learn More Page&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;qr-code-scanner&quot;&gt;QR Code Scanner&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper-prototype-qrscan.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;QR Scanner&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;QR Scanner&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incident:&lt;/strong&gt; While trying to “fake” taking a scan of the QR code, our user noted that he didn’t really know where to put the QR code, and that it would be nice to have a box on the camera screen so the user knows exactly where to put it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Severity Level:&lt;/strong&gt; 1&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Revision:&lt;/strong&gt; Simply adding a box/grid layout to make it easier for the user.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/pp-cam-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Updated QR code screen&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;discussion&quot;&gt;Discussion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper-prototype-discussion-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Discussion&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Discussion&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incident:&lt;/strong&gt; This was a positive incident; our user was quickly and easily able to locate the “discussion” section and understand the gist of the interface and how it would operate. This is likely because discussions like this exist in similar formats on other platforms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;favoriting&quot;&gt;Favoriting&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/favorite_old.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Old Favorite&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 50%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Old favorite button&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incident:&lt;/strong&gt; Favoriting and adding artworks to the user’s profile was not readily apparent. Although participant 2 was able to discover this feature after exploring the application and browsing his user profile, the discovery was only in hindsight after he had already left the artwork profile screen. This incident was negative. Because favoriting artworks is one of our six primary tasks and the main feature of the user profile, this feature needed to be made more obvious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Severity Level:&lt;/strong&gt; 4&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Revisions:&lt;/strong&gt; Our solution was to change the favorite button into a more visible “like” button right underneath the work’s title. We also added some more explicit text to make this functionality even more obvious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/favorite_new.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;New Favorite&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 50%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;New favorite button&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;museum-profile&quot;&gt;Museum Profile&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incident:&lt;/strong&gt; Upon opening the application and being shown the initial screen for the “Search mode,” both participants two and three first went to the “Museum Profile” for the purposes of initially exploring the application. This incident was negative, as the order of interaction was not intuitive to our test users. Starting with the museum profile as the launch page may be more ideal; it places the app within the user’s settings by communicating that the app is museum-specific and clearly defining what artwork is covered. Although not directly part of a primary task, the museum profile orients the user toward accomplishing the task of searching art pieces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Severity Level:&lt;/strong&gt; 4&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Revisions:&lt;/strong&gt; Creating a “Launch Screen” that will make more sense to the user.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/ppf_homepage.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;homepage&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 50%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Launch screen&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;user-vocabulary&quot;&gt;User Vocabulary&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/search_old.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Old Search&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 50%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Old search syntax&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/threads_old.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Old Thread&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 50%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Old thread syntax&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incident:&lt;/strong&gt; Some of the syntax employed resulted in negative incidents, as they did not successfully translate their ascribed functionality. In particular, at the search page, participant 3 didn’t understand the difference between being in the “Search” mode and the button option to “Search.” Additionally, she did not recognize that the “Threads” section of the User Profile would display the threads she participated in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Severity Level:&lt;/strong&gt; 1&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Revisions:&lt;/strong&gt; Changing these words so that they better suit the user’s vocabulary to increase the usability of these key interactions. We changed the text for searching by text to “Text Search” instead of just “Search,” and changed the “Threads” tab to say “Your Threads”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/search_new.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;New Search&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 50%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;New search syntax&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/threads_new.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;New Thread&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 50%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;New thread syntax&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;qr-code-search-tutorial&quot;&gt;QR Code Search Tutorial&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/tutorial_old.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Old Tutorial&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 50%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Old initial search screen&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incident:&lt;/strong&gt; Both participants two and three did not understand the capability to scan QR codes, which was another negative incident. However, once this feature of being able to scan the QR codes displayed on artwork placards was explained to them, both preferred to use this over the text search.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Severity Level:&lt;/strong&gt; 2&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Revisions:&lt;/strong&gt; To solve this problem of not effectively communicating the ability to use QR codes to look up artworks, upon launching the “Search” mode for the first time, a tutorial overlay page outlines the QR code look-up process for the user.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/tutorial_new.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;New Tutorial&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 50%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;New initial search screen&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;overview-of-revised-prototype&quot;&gt;Overview of Revised Prototype&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/overview-pic-updated.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Revised Overview&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Revised paper prototype overview&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The application has three primary modes: the museum profile, search, and user profile. The yellow highlighted box indicates which mode the user is in. Initially opening the application brings the user to the Museum profile mode page, as shown below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/ppf_homepage.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;homepage&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 50%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Launch screen&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;primary-tasks&quot;&gt;Primary Tasks&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;task-1-learn-more-context-and-background-information-to-better-understand-the-meaning-behind-artworks&quot;&gt;Task 1: Learn more context and background information to better understand the meaning behind artworks&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the launch page, users can start their search. Opening the Search mode for the first time prompts a tutorial, as shown in Screen 1.1.0, detailing how to look up an image using a QR code. In Screen 1.1.1, users can then choose between a text (Screens 1.2-1.3) or QR search (Screens 1.4-1.6). Both lead to a results page, in Screen 1.7, where the desired artwork can be chosen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper_prototyping_search.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Revised Search&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Revised search&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clicking on the artwork opens a nested art profile page with “About,” “Learn More,” and “Discussion” tabs the user can toggle between to support the first task of discovering more context about artworks. The “About” tab contains drop-down menus of further background information, including “Context,” “Inspiration,” “Genre,” and “Related Works” that can be collapsed and expanded. Shown below is a work flow that allows the user to explore information, and identify the inspiration section specifically.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/favorite_new.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;First screen on artwork profile: about page&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/pp-about-inspo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;User clicks on inspiration&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/pp-learn-more.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;User clicks on Learn More&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;task-2-discuss-artwork-with-others-in-order-to-further-engage-with-the-pieces&quot;&gt;Task 2: Discuss artwork with others in order to further engage with the pieces&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper_prototyping_art_profile_2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Revised Art Profile 2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Art profile (cont.)&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The “Discussion” tab (Screen 2.6) supports the task of discussing art with others. In this tab, users can post and reply to other users’ comments about this artwork, as shown in Screens 2.7-10.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper_prototyping_user_profile.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Revised User Profile&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;User profile&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clicking on the User Profile mode displays the initial Screen 3.1. The user profile displays a header containing a user profile picture, name, and bio. The body of the page consist of “Favorites” and “Threads” tabs. The “Favorites” tab displays favorited artworks. Clicking on any of these artworks, in Screen 3.2, brings the user to a nested art profile page, in Screen 3.3. The “Threads” tab (Screen 3.5) displays a list of discussions the user has participated in and highlights those with unread replies. Clicking on any of these comments, in Screen 3.6, opens a nested discussion page, as shown in Screen 3.7.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;key-revisions&quot;&gt;Key Revisions&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the key revisions we made was the search functionality. First, we added in clear and large buttons to delineate the difference between the text search and the QR search. Then we added more explicit text so that the users could distinguish between the kinds of search and understand why they were different. Lastly, we added in a one-time tutorial of how the QR search functionality would work. All of these changes helped make the search function much clearer and improve the usability. Since searching for the artwork to pull up its artwork profile is a key functionality of our design, this was very important to us to change. Another key revision was changing how the “About” and “Learn More” pages were divided, and we found that after the first usability test, we needed to make this distinction more intuitive. We decided to modify what kinds of information would be located under each tab. We noticed in our second and third usability tests, this distinction was a lot more clear to our users, and they had no problem finding what they needed with this modification. Thus, we found this change to be incredibly important for our design and usability. Obviously, since finding background information is a key task we are trying to support, making it as easy as possible for the user to find the background information they are explicitly looking for is important to us. Lastly, adding the launch page to be the museum profile was a key revision for us, because it helps orient the user and helps her understand what the other tabs are for. We didn’t realize that the “Museum Profile” tab might be confusing to the user if they are not brought their first, so this was another key revision. It helps the user build a correct “mental model” of how the app works.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Usability Testing Check-In</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/usability-testing-check-in/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Usability Testing Check-In" /><published>2018-04-12T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-04-12T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/usability-testing-check-in</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/usability-testing-check-in/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;heuristic-evaluation&quot;&gt;Heuristic Evaluation&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our group received two heuristic evaluations from two different groups. The evaluation was carried out according to Nielsen’s heuristics sheet. The evaluators identified potential issues with our design, noted the heuristic violated, and assigned a severity score. For detailed images of the evaluator’s comments, refer to the &lt;a href=&quot;../heuristic-evaluations&quot;&gt;Heuristic Evaluations page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;list-of-issues-and-modifications&quot;&gt;List of issues and modifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;1-functionality-of-camera-icon-is-unclear&quot;&gt;1. Functionality of Camera Icon is Unclear&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper-prototype-search.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Search menu&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We received feedback that a primary function of our application, which allows the user to scan a QR code using the mobile phone’s camera, was not clear. The camera icon was too close to the search bar, and the camera did not provide any indication that it would be used to scan QR codes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heuristic Violated:&lt;/strong&gt; This issue violates the visibility of system heuristic. Providing more clarity on the different functions of the search bar and the camera icon, through labeling and separation of the two components, will provide better context for the user.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Severity Rating:&lt;/strong&gt; 3&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Revision:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/pp-cam-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Two separated components with clear labeling&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;2-missing-back-buttons&quot;&gt;2. Missing Back Button(s)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper-prototype-inspo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Inspiration section of “Learn more” &lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our evaluators pointed out that after navigating to inspiration, it was unclear how to get back to the main about section. They felt stuck.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heuristic Violated:&lt;/strong&gt;  User Control and freedom. Our design did not have a clearly market “emergency exit” there.  We added in a back button.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Severity Rating:&lt;/strong&gt; 1&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Revisions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/pp-about-inspo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Back button added&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;3--redundancy&quot;&gt;3.  Redundancy&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper-prototype-cam.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;About&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Camera screen&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper-prototype-discuss.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Learn More&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Discussion screen&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some of our screen components, like the bottom toolbar, felt redundant to our evaluators in certain contexts. This added clutter and made the design difficult to navigate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heuristic Violated:&lt;/strong&gt; Aesthetics and minimalist design. The design should only provide information that is needed and is helpful to the user. We decided to drop the bottom bar wherever it was easy for the user to still go back one page and find the bottom bar easily should they need it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Severity Rating:&lt;/strong&gt; 2&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Revisions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/pp-cam-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;About&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Camera screen removes toolbar&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/pp-discuss.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Learn More&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Discussion screen removes toolbar&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;4-lack-of-feedback&quot;&gt;4. Lack of Feedback&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper-prototype-faves.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Learn More&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Favorites section&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the evaluators liked the feature that allowed users to favorite paintings. However, it was not clear to them how and where the favored artworks were stored within the application.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heuristic Violated:&lt;/strong&gt; Match between system and real world. While our application stored the artworks favorited by the user, it did not provide enough feedback to the user. People expect an action to have a visible reaction. However, we have decided to not make the user profile section our focus right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Severity Rank:&lt;/strong&gt; 1&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;usability-test-results&quot;&gt;Usability Test Results&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We conducted the first usability test with a senior at Williams, in a study room in Sawyer Library. We chose to start with him because he is not an art history major but has taken four art history classes at Williams and has a deep appreciation for art, so he sits in the middle in terms of art education. We followed the test protocol outlined in Kathleen Gomoll’s “Some Techniques for Observing Users,” starting with a brief explanation of the app and the format and rules for the usability test. We explained each of our two main tasks in a scenario format for the user, and asked him to carry out those tasks while explaining his thought process and ask questions (even if we couldn’t answer them). Stephanie facilitated the usability test, and Joyce took notes. A major challenge we encountered while facilitating the usability test was “the user with an agenda,” as Carolyn Snyder describes it in “Paper Prototyping.” I believe there are several reasons for why our participant believed he was being asked his opinion on the app’s interface and to describe what he liked and disliked. For one, I think we can be more clear going forward with regards to establishing what the purpose of the usability test is. We may have underestimated the possibility of this happening. I also believe the fact that the user was easily able to understand the app’s functionality meant he ended up sort of looking for other things to talk about or comment on. We also did not write out the tasks this time, and I think going forward it will be helpful to print out the tasks so that the user can see very explicitly what his direction is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;critical-incidents&quot;&gt;Critical Incidents&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;about-vs-learn-more&quot;&gt;“About” vs “Learn More”&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper-prototype-about.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;About&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;About screen under artwork profile&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper-prototype-learnmore.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Learn More&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Learn More screen under artwork profile&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incident:&lt;/strong&gt; While trying to navigate to a page that contained the inspiration for an artwork, we realized that it wasn’t clear to a general user whether the inspiration information should be under “about” or “learn more.” This led us to believe we may want to put more information about the inspiration and context under the “about” tab, and leave very in-depth understanding to the “learn more” section (e.g. further information about the artist and the history of the movement).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Severity Level:&lt;/strong&gt; 3 (This is one of the main tasks our app is trying to support).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Revision:&lt;/strong&gt; Modifying the “Learn More” section to be a series of very in-depth information and having the “About” page contain information that used to be in the “Learn More” section.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/pp-about.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;New About Page&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/pp-learn-more.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;New Learn More Page&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;qr-code-scanner&quot;&gt;QR Code Scanner&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper-prototype-qrscan.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;QR Scanner&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;QR Scanner&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incident:&lt;/strong&gt; While trying to “fake” taking a scan of the QR code, our user noted that he didn’t really know where to put the QR code, and that it would be nice to have a box on the camera screen so the user knows exactly where to put it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Severity Level:&lt;/strong&gt; 1&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Revision:&lt;/strong&gt; Simply adding a box/grid layout to make it easier for the user.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/pp-cam-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Updated QR code screen&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;discussion&quot;&gt;Discussion&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper-prototype-discussion-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Discussion&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Discussion&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incident:&lt;/strong&gt; This was a positive incident; our user was quickly and easily able to locate the “discussion” section and understand the gist of the interface and how it would operate. This is likely because discussions like this exist in similar formats on other platforms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;updated-design&quot;&gt;Updated Design&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/pp-overview.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Overview&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Overview of Revised Prototype&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;task-1-finding-background-information&quot;&gt;Task 1: Finding background information&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/pp-cam-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;User begins in search function&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/pp-cam-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;User chooses QR code scan&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/pp-qr.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;User scans QR code&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/pp-about.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;App scans QR and navigates to artwork profile, beginning in About section&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/pp-about-inspo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;User clicks on inspiration&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/pp-learn-more.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;User clicks on Learn More&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;task-2-discussing-art-with-others&quot;&gt;Task 2: Discussing art with others&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/pp-about.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;User begins on front page of artwork’s profile&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/pp-discuss.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;User clicks on Discussion and writes a brief comment&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/pp-discuss-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;cam&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;User submits comment, and it shows up at the top of the comments section&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;going-forward&quot;&gt;Going Forward&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For our next usability tests, we may try to recruit an older person, although this will admittedly be much harder to do. Professors are generally busy, and we don’t know many older members of the community. If we cannot find an older user, we will still try to recruit people from different demographic backgrounds. We will try to recruit at least one user who is very well-versed in art history and art, and one who is not very interested in art and only consumes art through museums. We will try to rotate roles for the remaining tests so that everyone gets a chance at trying out each role. We have already mentioned some things we will try to change for upcoming usability tests, with the major one being establishing very up front that we are not exactly looking for the participant’s opinion on our interfaces during usability testing. We will also print out instructions for the tasks going forward.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Heuristic Evaluations</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/heuristic-evaluations/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Heuristic Evaluations" /><published>2018-04-09T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-04-09T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/heuristic-evaluations</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/heuristic-evaluations/">&lt;p&gt;Stephanie and Joyce facilitated an heuristic evaluation performed by Karl on our paper prototype (and vice versa for Pin’s prototype). His full evaluation is below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/heuristic-karl-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Karl&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Karl's written evaluation&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cliff facilitated an evaluation performed by Alyssa and Lester (and vice versa for Pin’s prototype). Their full evaluations are below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/heuristic-alyssa-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Alyssa&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Alyssa's written evaluation&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/heuristic-lester-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lester&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Lester's written evaluation&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An overview image of the paper prototype we used for evaluation is also shown below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper_prototyping_overview.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Overview&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Components of paper prototype&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To see the evaluations we performed on Pin’s paper prototype, please refer to Pin’s project page.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Paper Prototyping</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/paper-prototype/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Paper Prototyping" /><published>2018-04-04T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-04-04T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/paper-prototype</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/paper-prototype/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;design&quot;&gt;Design&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Art for All is a mobile application that allows users to learn more about the art pieces users see in museums&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tasks&quot;&gt;Tasks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Learn more context and background information to better understand the meaning behind artworks&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Discuss artwork with others in order further engage with the pieces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;overview-of-paper-prototyping&quot;&gt;Overview of paper prototyping&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper_prototyping_overview.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Overview&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Components of paper prototype&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The application has three primary modes: the museum profile, search, and user profile. The yellow highlighted box indicates which mode the user is in. Initially opening the application brings the user to the default Search mode page, as shown in Screen 1.1. From this page, users have the option between either a text search, as shown in Screens 1.2, 1.3, or a picture QR code search, as shown in Screens 1.4, 1.5, 1.6 Both lead to a results page, in Screen 1.7, where the desired artwork can be chosen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper_prototyping_ search.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Search&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Searching artwork&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clicking on the artwork opens a nested art profile page with “About” (Screen 2.1), “Learn More,” and “Discussion” tabs the user can toggle between to support the first task of discovering more context about artworks. The “Learn More” tab (Screen 2.3) contains drop-down menus of further background information, including “Context,” “Inspiration,” “History,” and “Genre” that can be collapsed and expanded, as shown in Screen 2.5.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper_prototyping_ art_profile_1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Art Prof 1&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Artwork Profile&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper_prototyping_ art_profile_2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Art Prof 2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Artwork Profile (cont.)&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The “Discussion” tab (Screen 2.7) supports the task of discussing art with others. In this tab, users can post and reply to other users’ comments about this artwork, as shown in Screens 2.8-12.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/paper_prototyping_ user_profile.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;User Profile&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;User Profile&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clicking on the User Profile mode displays the initial Screen 3.1. The user profile displays a header containing a user profile picture, name, and bio. The body of the page consist of “Favorites” and “Threads” tabs that are toggled between. The “Favorites” tab displays favorited artworks. Clicking on any of these artworks, in Screen 3.2, brings the user to a nested art profile page, in Screen 3.3. The “Threads” tab (Screen 3.5) displays a list of discussions the user has participated in and highlights those with unread replies. Clicking on any of these comments, in Screen 3.6, opens a nested discussion page, as shown in Screen 3.7.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Final Report</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Final-Report/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Final Report" /><published>2018-04-04T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-04-04T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Final-Report</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Final-Report/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;project&quot;&gt;Project&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Art for All: An interactive and educational platform for public engagement at art museums&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;team-members-all-generalists&quot;&gt;Team Members (all generalists):&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cliff Makanda, Stephanie Liu, Joyce Wang&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;problem-and-solution-overview&quot;&gt;Problem and Solution Overview:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Art museums have long been a primary resource for learning about and experiencing art. Unfortunately, art can often feel intimidatingly inaccessible for the general public. For regular people, who aren’t academics or involved in the “art world,” art can feel elusive, out-of-touch, or even perhaps just confusing. Without a formal introduction to art, which is generally only available to the privileged, it becomes difficult to glean much insight from abstract and unfamiliar artworks. This problem stems from both the little information museums provide about artworks as well as the lack of informal resources available for engaging in conversations about art. Art for All intends to overcome these hurdles by providing a simple and easy-to-use framework for finding background information about artworks and artists, and allowing users to engage in informal discussions about specific artworks online. In this way, users from a diverse set of backgrounds can come together to discuss their varied interpretations of art to get a better understanding of how art can impact their lives. In addition, background information will be readily accessible and easy to understand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;design-research-goals-stakeholders-and-participants&quot;&gt;Design Research: Goals, Stakeholders, and Participants&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This &lt;a href=&quot;../design-research-goals-stakeholders-and-participants&quot;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; provides information about the methods and process we used for gathering design research through interviews and contextual inquiries, as well as detailed accounts of the participants, their backgrounds, and the environments in which they were interviewed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;design-research-results-and-themes&quot;&gt;Design Research: Results and Themes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This &lt;a href=&quot;../design-research-results-and-themes&quot;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; provides an overview of the key results and themes from our design research, as found through affinity diagramming. The emergence of these key themes allowed us to guide our design to specifically tailor user needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;task-analysis&quot;&gt;Task Analysis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This &lt;a href=&quot;../task-analysis&quot;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; details our answers to specific task analysis questions, and allows us to set the scope of our design as it relates to the users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;proposed-design-sketches-3x4&quot;&gt;Proposed Design Sketches (“3x4”)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This &lt;a href=&quot;../Proposed-Design-Sketches-3-x-4&quot;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; presents three different potential design choices, and details the specific tasks they are designed to support. An updated design is presented at the end, with an explanation for why that specific design was ultimately chosen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;written-scenarios-1x2&quot;&gt;Written Scenarios (“1x2”)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This &lt;a href=&quot;../Written-Scenarios-1-x-2&quot;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; details the two selected tasks we chose to support in our final design, and written scenarios for each task that correspond to the storyboards as presented in the next section.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;storyboards&quot;&gt;Storyboards&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This &lt;a href=&quot;../Storyboards&quot;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; presents the two storyboards that correspond to our selected tasks.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Storyboards</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Storyboards/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Storyboards" /><published>2018-03-12T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-03-12T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Storyboards</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Storyboards/">&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/storyboard-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Storyboard 1&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Storyboard 1: Finding background information task &lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/storyboard-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Storyboard 2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Storyboard 2: Participating in online discussions about art task&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Written Scenarios (“1x2”)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Written-Scenarios-1-x-2/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Written Scenarios (“1x2”)" /><published>2018-03-11T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-03-11T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Written-Scenarios-1-x-2</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Written-Scenarios-1-x-2/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;selected-supported-tasks&quot;&gt;Selected Supported Tasks&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our two selected tasks are finding background information about an artwork, and engaging in online discussions focused on specific artworks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finding background information is an activity that is central to the museum experience. We found during our contextual inquiries that all of the people we talked to came to the museum to learn about art, although some emphasized different aspects of that learning. In either case, we definitely wanted to highlight this learning aspect in our app.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the discussion side, we mostly interviewed people who were already in groups, and we noticed how they enjoyed talking to each other about the art as they went along. The discussion task will thus allow for a wider conversation to take place with a more diverse set of people. In addition, people who find themselves visiting a museum alone will still get to discuss their experience with others. Art is a social experience. A museum-goer should not only be able to communicate with an artwork but also with other museum-goers. This allows for cross pollination of ideas and different interpretations of art.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;scenarios&quot;&gt;Scenarios&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;scenario-1-finding-background-information&quot;&gt;Scenario 1: Finding background information&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ben is visiting his local art museum and comes across a piece that really strikes him. He wants to know more, so he pulls up the Art for All app and navigates to the search tab. He clicks on the camera button and scans a picture of the QR code on the artworks’ panel. The app pulls up the artworks’ profile, and he clicks on the Learn More tab. He wants to learn about the inspiration for the piece, so he clicks on the Inspiration section and reads about the artists’ inspiration for the work. When he has read as much info as he’d like to know, he closes the app and moves on to investigate more in the museum. See &lt;a href=&quot;../Storyboards&quot;&gt;Storyboard 1&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;scenario-2-discussing-art&quot;&gt;Scenario 2: Discussing Art&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bob has recently visited a museum and become entranced with a Jackson Pollock work. He is waiting for the bus, and thinks back to this piece. He decides he wants to discuss this particular artwork with others, so he pulls up the Art for All app and navigates to the discussion section under this artwork profile page. He asks some probing questions, and finds that another student, Sarah, is also online at the same time and wants to talk about this particular work. They discuss their interpretations, and in the end Bob feels like he has a better understanding of the artwork. See &lt;a href=&quot;../Storyboards&quot;&gt;Storyboard 2&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Proposed Design Sketches (“3x4”)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Proposed-Design-Sketches-3-x-4/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Proposed Design Sketches (“3x4”)" /><published>2018-03-07T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-03-07T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Proposed-Design-Sketches-3-x-4</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Proposed-Design-Sketches-3-x-4/">&lt;p&gt;Note: See the &lt;a href=&quot;../Supported-Tasks&quot;&gt;supported tasks&lt;/a&gt; page for information about the tasks referenced here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;first-design&quot;&gt;First Design&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/steph-sketch-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Stephanie’s Sketch&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Sketch of first design&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tasks:&lt;/strong&gt; Background information, contexts, discussion, favoriting, and remembering&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Main Idea:&lt;/strong&gt; This design focuses on how we might layout a particular “art profile” and the discovery of new information about the artwork, as well as user and artist profiles. The artwork is presented as a central page, where “about”, “learn more”, and “discussion” are the main focuses and the user can tab between them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Tasks 1 &amp;amp; 4) Learning:&lt;/strong&gt; The “about” tab includes a placard-like explanation. The “learn more” tab on the artwork’s profile allows the user to make an individual choice about which aspect of the background information she’d like to explore through a series of tabbed pages. Elliot, who likes history, can specifically choose the history tab. In addition, there is a small “progress bar” at the bottom that allows the user to navigate to more information if their curiosity is not yet satisfied. Logan, who wants to learn about the inspiration, can navigate to the “inspiration” section.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Tasks 2, 5, 8) &lt;em&gt;Discussion:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; The “discussion” tab on the artwork’s profile allows the users to talk with each other and with scholars and artists in the field to learn about the artwork in a more informal/colloquial setting. Both Anna and Caroline can use this functionality to hear about others’ experiences. The scholars/artists who participate in the discussion will have special annotations on their icons to indicate that they are professionals in their field, and the particular artist of the work will have a distinct icon so they can reliably answer questions that come up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Task 6) &lt;em&gt;Favoriting Artworks:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; On the “art profile,” there is a button on the upper-right corner (the heart) that allows the users to favorite the work they are looking at. In addition, on the user profile page, Chelsea can look through her past favorites in the “favorites” tab, and also look at an overview of what her favorite pieces were like in the “about” tab. The “about” tab will show her what the breakdown of her favorite artworks is, by genre, time period, or possibly any number of things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Task 3) &lt;em&gt;Remembering Artworks:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; In the user profile, there will be a tab for “favorites.” The user can then look through the artworks they favorited and reflect on what they’ve enjoyed the most in the past. Carlos can use this functionality to keep tabs on all his favorite works, and learn more about them from the comfort of his own home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;second-design&quot;&gt;Second Design&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tasks:&lt;/strong&gt; finding background information, breaking down formal art terms, getting more context,
artist communicating with people about the work&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Main Idea:&lt;/strong&gt; This design is museum-centric. The mobile application is museum-specific and primarily for real-time use while visiting museums. The design allows users to more easily access information about art pieces that are sometimes available in museums, currently in the form of wall text and pamphlets, but now more directly in a centralized source. It provides streamlined, simple information about the piece. This design provides a text search option, a QR code search option, favorites page, and a location-based map of the museum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/joyce-sketch-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Joyce’s Sketch&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Sketch of second design: Main navigation&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Task 1) &lt;em&gt;Reading placards and finding background information about artworks:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
The search and QR scan options allow users to quickly find the pages for artworks. All artwork pages include an image of the work and ID information, such as title, artist, date, etc, that might usually be placed on placards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/joyce-sketch-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Joyce’s Sketch 2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Sketch of second design: Art Profile&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Tasks 1 &amp;amp; 4) &lt;em&gt;Understanding more context about art pieces:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
Scrolling down the Artwork Page reveals a two-tab menu option with “Description” (a brief analysis/explanation of the work) and “Artist” (an artist’s statement on the piece). Elliot and Logan can choose the “Description” tab when they want to learn more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Task 7) &lt;em&gt;Breaking down formal art interpretations into understandable terms:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
The “Description” tab also includes links to basic terms, such as “Surrealism,” which links to a nested page with a definition of the term in easy-to-understand language that Syd can use to develop more understanding about art.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Task 8) &lt;em&gt;Artist communicating to people interested in her work:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
The artist tab includes what the artist would like his/her audience to know about the specific work. Jordan can use this to explain additional information if questions come up. If the artist is current enough, the artist name links to a nested Artist Page, where background information about the artist is provided.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;third-design&quot;&gt;Third Design&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/cliff-sketch-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Cliff’s Sketch&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Sketch of third design&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tasks:&lt;/strong&gt; Understanding more context about art, discussing art with museum experts and novices, Finding background information about art.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Main Idea:&lt;/strong&gt; This design is focused connecting the artist to the museum-goer to enhance the latter’s understanding of an artist’s work. It also introduces a digital space to chat with the artist, other museum-goers, and art experts. The design is designed to be mobile-centric.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Task 4) &lt;em&gt;Understanding Context:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; The main page shows an artist’s profile. It goes into more depth than the traditional wall text or placard. At the top of the page is the artists name, below that we have the image of the artist. The image is followed by a link to the artist’s works. A brief but thorough description of the artist forms the main content of the page. A museum goer like Logan can get more context about an artwork by getting insights from the artists biography.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Task 1) &lt;em&gt;Background Information:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; After clicking the “works” link indicated above, a user is presented with a picture gallery of all the works by an artist. A user like Elliot who wants to understand the background of an artwork can see an artist’s work in relation to other works by the same artist. Clicking on an artwork will further lead to a page about the artwork that offers more detail and context.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Task 2) &lt;em&gt;Discussion with fellow museum-goers:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Below an artwork’s description is a chat bubble with a link that leads to a digital space that fosters discussion among the artist, museum-goers, and scholars in the field. The user is able to ask questions about an artwork and respond to other users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Task 5 &amp;amp; 8) &lt;em&gt;Discussion with experts and artist:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; On top of the discussion page is a list of most recent answers from an artist. Below that is a list of experts. A user can read past discussion and post questions. He is able to interact with both the artist and experts (if he chooses to).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;updated-design&quot;&gt;Updated Design&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We decided to combine parts of each of the first two designs in our final design. The second museum-centered design will serve as the basis for our app’s structure. The motivation for this choice came from our contextual inquiries, because we realized that most people don’t actually look at or find art on their own; they come to museums for that purpose. We chose to keep the map from the second design because our contextual inquiries revealed that navigating effectively through museums and from one exhibit to the next can be a challenge for people. We also kept the QR codes featured in that design, because we noticed when visiting MASS MoCA that many modern exhibits these days aren’t just framed artworks, so they would be harder to detect by just snapping a picture. In addition, some exhibits don’t allow camera use inside, so the QR code could be placed just outside the exhibit with the wall text. From the first design, we wanted to keep the tabs that toggle between “About”, “Learn More” and “Discussion,” because we didn’t feel like there was a streamlined sequence of events for people when viewing an artwork (i.e. they didn’t first read the background, then ask questions, and then discuss the art; they often went back and forth).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/updated-design-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Updated Interface&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/updated-design-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Updated Interface&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Updated Design&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;!--## Citations
1. [Dorothea Lange's &quot;Migrant Mother&quot; Photographs in the Farm Security Administration Collection: An Overview](http://www.loc.gov/rr/print/list/128_migm.html)--&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Supported Tasks</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Supported-Tasks/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Supported Tasks" /><published>2018-03-06T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-03-06T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Supported-Tasks</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Supported-Tasks/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;existing-tasks&quot;&gt;Existing Tasks:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;1-reading-placards-and-finding-background-information-about-artworks---hard-task&quot;&gt;1. &lt;em&gt;Reading placards and finding background information about artworks&lt;/em&gt; - Hard task&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Elliot is a junior majoring in history at Amherst. He likes going to museums to learn about history from a visual perspective, and he decides to attend a local art museum on the weekend. He sees an 18th century piece he really likes and reads the placard, but it names only the artist, date, and title of the work, and there is only explanatory wall text for the featured exhibits. He appreciates the art for what it is but feels he is missing part of the puzzle by not knowing anything about the connection between the artist and the work, and especially the history behind it. He writes down the name of the artwork for later, and continues on. When he returns from the museum, he googles the title of the piece hoping to learn more about it. Unfortunately, the artwork he liked so much was made by a lesser-known artist, so there isn’t much on the Internet about it. He does find a few scholarly articles about the artist, but they’re filled with confusing language and art terminology that he doesn’t understand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;2-discussing-art-with-others-in-person---moderate-task&quot;&gt;2. &lt;em&gt;Discussing art with others in person&lt;/em&gt; - Moderate task&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anna is a frequent attender of museums, and likes to explore new kinds of art. She visits a contemporary art exhibit with a group of friends in a new city. As they’re walking around, a passer-by suggests they go up close to look at the exhibit featuring mirrors, because it provides a different perspective. As they take turns looking at themselves in the reflections, they share thoughts about the experience, and they notice that they all have different opinions on the installation based on their experiences with looking at their own reflections. They feel they have learned about themselves, about each other, and about the power of art to make us think about ourselves, through this discussion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;3-appreciating-and-remembering-art-after-a-museum-visit---easy-task&quot;&gt;3. &lt;em&gt;Appreciating and remembering art after a museum visit&lt;/em&gt; - Easy task&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Carlos loves visiting museums, and he finds that certain artworks spark something in him that he just can’t describe. For these pieces, he tries to write them down somewhere so he can remember them for later–sometimes in a journal, sometimes in his “Notes” app on his phone. If the piece is part of a permanent exhibit, he jots that down too so he can visit it again the next time he comes to that museum. He also sometimes buys postcards or artist booklets at the museum so he can appreciate the art and look back on it even after he’s left the museum, but those can get pretty expensive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;new-tasks&quot;&gt;New Tasks:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;4-understanding-more-context-about-art-pieces---hard-task&quot;&gt;4. &lt;em&gt;Understanding more context about art pieces&lt;/em&gt; - Hard task&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Logan is visiting New York and decides to visit the famous MoMA, but he doesn’t know much about art and has no formal art training. He’s looking at the famous “Migrant Mother” photograph, and the placard notes that it was taken in 1963 in Nipomo, California by Dorothea Lange, but he gets no other information. He can feel the desperation in the image, but wants to learn more. Who is the woman in the photograph and why does she look like she’s suffering? He navigates to the photograph’s profile on the app and reads some basic information about the artwork. He learns that Lange was spending a month photographing migratory farm labor when she took this shot. He reads Lange’s account of her experience, and learns that the mother in the photograph “said that they had been living on frozen vegetables from the surrounding fields, and birds that the children killed. She had just sold the tires from her car to buy food.”&lt;sup&gt;[1]&lt;/sup&gt; Logan feels like he can now better understand the emotional energy of the photograph.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;5-discussing-art-with-museum-experts-and-novices---moderate-task&quot;&gt;5. &lt;em&gt;Discussing art with museum experts and novices&lt;/em&gt; - Moderate task&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Caroline is a flight attendant for a major airline company. Every now and then she finds herself stuck in a major city with nothing to do. To pass the time before her next assignment, she often visits museums. She does not have any formal background in art, and would rather spend her time at home with her children than reading books on art. Because she’s usually away for work in random cities, she doesn’t always have friends to go to museums with, but she still wants to discuss the art with “regular” people and potentially scholars if they use colloquial language. At her next stop in Toledo, she visits an art museum, and finds a really interesting abstract art piece that she doesn’t quite understand. She doesn’t really want to spend time reading about background information; she finds that process kind of boring. Instead, she navigates to the artwork’s profile on the app, and reads about other people’s experiences with the piece. She is fascinated with how others describe their experiences with art, and the language they use to convey their emotions. She is also impressed by the insights she gains by reading responses from scholars who use colloquial language. She is surprised to find that people took on very varied interpretations of the art, and slowly begins to develop the confidence to decide for herself what the artwork means to her. She even adds her own comment, and feels pride in participating in this discussion and adding her own take.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;6-favoriting-artworks---easy-task&quot;&gt;6. &lt;em&gt;Favoriting artworks&lt;/em&gt; - Easy task&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chelsea is an avid art-lover, and loves visiting art museums in her spare time. She visits a new museum that just opened in her city, and stumbles upon a painting that she is immediately entranced by. She wants to remember this artwork somehow, so that she can look back on it later and remember how it made her feel. She uses the app to navigate to the painting’s profile and “favorite” it. That night at home, she thinks more about the painting and other artworks that have impacted her. She pulls up the app to see all of the artworks she’s favorited in the past. She goes through some of them, and nostalgically remembers how she felt at each time, and even thinks about the context in her life when each of these artworks was particularly meaningful to her. As she scrolls through, she notices that most of the artworks she’s favorited have been paintings and abstract art, and feels like she’s learned something about her own personal style of expression through this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;extra-tasks&quot;&gt;Extra Tasks:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;7-breaking-down-formal-art-interpretations-into-understandable-terms---hard-task-existing&quot;&gt;7. &lt;em&gt;Breaking down formal art interpretations into understandable terms&lt;/em&gt; - Hard task (Existing)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Syd has had no formal experience studying art and so is not familiar with the formal terms used to describe art. However, she enjoys going to art museums on the weekend with her friends. On one visit, the pamphlets about the artworks use a lot of formal language she doesn’t understand. She asks her friends what they mean. However, there are some parts that are not understandable to her friends either. In these cases, she uses her phone to google each term, and after identifying appropriate definitions, she is able to piece together what the pamphlet is talking about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;8-artist-communicating-with-people-interested-in-her-work---moderate-task-new&quot;&gt;8. &lt;em&gt;Artist communicating with people interested in her work&lt;/em&gt; - Moderate task (New)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jordan Mitchell is a rising modern artist with a number of nationwide exhibitions. Her artwork is revolutionary and can be hard to understand for both art novices and experts. She often attends museum events, explains her work, and interacts with people interested in her work. However, she is unable to attend as many events as she would like to. She communicates with both novice and experienced museum goers. She is able to explain her work, and respond to any of their questions. This helps breakdown the barriers preventing people to understand her revolutionary artwork. It is also a way for Jordan to get real time feedback on how people see her artworks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;citations&quot;&gt;Citations&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.loc.gov/rr/print/list/128_migm.html&quot;&gt;Dorothea Lange’s “Migrant Mother” Photographs in the Farm Security Administration Collection: An Overview&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry></feed>