<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.6.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-03-11T23:57:37-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/</id><title type="html">CSCI376 Project: Art for All</title><subtitle>Collaborative platform for artistic engagement</subtitle><author><name>Art for All</name></author><entry><title type="html">Project Design Review (“1x2”)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Project-Design-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Project Design Review (“1x2”)" /><published>2018-03-11T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-03-11T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Project-Design-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/Project-Design-Review/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;updated-design&quot;&gt;Updated Design&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We decided to combine parts of each of the first two designs in our final design. We decided to use the second museum-centered design as the basis for our app because when we did our contextual inquiries, we realized that most people don’t actually look at or find art on their own; they come to museums for that purpose. We also wanted to keep the map from the second design because our contextual inquiries revealed that navigating effectively through museums and from one exhibit to the next can be a challenge for people. We also kept the QR codes featured in that design, because we noticed when visiting MASS MoCA that many modern exhibits these days aren’t just framed artworks, so they would be harder to detect by just snapping a picture. In addition, some exhibits don’t allow camera use inside, so the QR code could be placed just outside the exhibit with the wall text. From the first design, we wanted to keep the tabs that toggle between “About”, “Learn More” and “Discussion,” because we didn’t feel like there was a streamlined sequence of events for people when viewing an artwork (i.e. they didn’t first read the background, then ask questions, and then discuss the art; they often went back and forth).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/updated-interface.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Updated Interface&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/updated-interface-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Updated Interface&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Updated Design&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tasks&quot;&gt;Tasks&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our two selected tasks are finding background information about an artwork, and engaging in an online chat room focused on art discussion.
Finding background information is an activity that is central to the museum experience. We found during our contextual inquiries that all of the people we talked to came to the museum to learn about art, although some emphasized different aspects of that learning. In either case, we definitely wanted to highlight this learning aspect in our app.
For the discussion side, we mostly interviewed people who were already in groups, and we noticed how they enjoyed talking to each other about the art as they went along. The discussion task will thus allow for a wider conversation to take place with a more diverse set of people. In addition, people who find themselves visiting a museum alone will still get to discuss their experience. The user is put in conversation with the museum when he observes the museum, and finds background about an artwork. Art is a social experience. A museum-goer should not only be able to communicate with an artwork but with other museum-goers. This allows for cross pollination of ideas and different interpretations of art.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;storyboards&quot;&gt;Storyboards&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/storyboard-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Storyboard 1&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Storyboard 1: Finding background information task &lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/storyboard-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Storyboard 2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Storyboard 2: Participating in online discussions about art task&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author><summary type="html">“”</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Project Design Check-In (“3x4”)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/project-design-check-in-3-x-4/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Project Design Check-In (“3x4”)" /><published>2018-03-07T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-03-07T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/project-design-check-in-3-x-4</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/project-design-check-in-3-x-4/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;existing-tasks&quot;&gt;Existing Tasks:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;1-reading-placards-and-finding-background-information-about-artworks---hard-task&quot;&gt;1. &lt;em&gt;Reading placards and finding background information about artworks&lt;/em&gt; - Hard task&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Elliot is a junior majoring in history at Amherst. He likes going to museums to learn about history from a visual perspective, and he decides to attend a local art museum on the weekend. He sees an 18th century piece he really likes and reads the placard, but it names only the artist, date, and title of the work, and there is only explanatory wall text for the featured exhibits. He appreciates the art for what it is but feels he is missing part of the puzzle by not knowing anything about the connection between the artist and the work, and especially the history behind it. He writes down the name of the artwork for later, and continues on. When he returns from the museum, he googles the title of the piece hoping to learn more about it. Unfortunately, the artwork he liked so much was made by a lesser-known artist, so there isn’t much on the Internet about it. He does find a few scholarly articles about the artist, but they’re filled with confusing language and art terminology that he doesn’t understand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;2-discussing-art-with-others-in-person---moderate-task&quot;&gt;2. &lt;em&gt;Discussing art with others in person&lt;/em&gt; - Moderate task&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anna is a frequent attender of museums, and likes to explore new kinds of art. She visits a contemporary art exhibit with a group of friends in a new city. As they’re walking around, a passer-by suggests they go up close to look at the exhibit featuring mirrors, because it provides a different perspective. As they take turns looking at themselves in the reflections, they share thoughts about the experience, and they notice that they all have different opinions on the installation based on their experiences with looking at their own reflections. They feel they have learned about themselves, about each other, and about the power of art to make us think about ourselves, through this discussion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;3-appreciating-and-remembering-art-after-a-museum-visit---easy-task&quot;&gt;3. &lt;em&gt;Appreciating and remembering art after a museum visit&lt;/em&gt; - Easy task&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Carlos loves visiting museums, and he finds that certain artworks spark something in him that he just can’t describe. For these pieces, he tries to write them down somewhere so he can remember them for later–sometimes in a journal, sometimes in his “Notes” app on his phone. If the piece is part of a permanent exhibit, he jots that down too so he can visit it again the next time he comes to that museum. He also sometimes buys postcards or artist booklets at the museum so he can appreciate the art and look back on it even after he’s left the museum, but those can get pretty expensive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;new-tasks&quot;&gt;New Tasks:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;4-understanding-more-context-about-art-pieces---hard-task&quot;&gt;4. &lt;em&gt;Understanding more context about art pieces&lt;/em&gt; - Hard task&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Logan is visiting New York and decides to visit the famous MoMA, but he doesn’t know much about art and has no formal art training. He’s looking at the famous “Migrant Mother” photograph, and the placard notes that it was taken in 1963 in Nipomo, California by Dorothea Lange, but he gets no other information. He can feel the desperation in the image, but wants to learn more. Who is the woman in the photograph and why does she look like she’s suffering? He navigates to the photograph’s profile on the app and reads some basic information about the artwork. He learns that Lange was spending a month photographing migratory farm labor when she took this shot. He reads Lange’s account of her experience, and learns that the mother in the photograph “said that they had been living on frozen vegetables from the surrounding fields, and birds that the children killed. She had just sold the tires from her car to buy food.”&lt;sup&gt;[1]&lt;/sup&gt; Logan feels like he can now better understand the emotional energy of the photograph.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;5-discussing-art-with-museum-experts-and-novices---moderate-task&quot;&gt;5. &lt;em&gt;Discussing art with museum experts and novices&lt;/em&gt; - Moderate task&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Caroline is a flight attendant for a major airline company. Every now and then she finds herself stuck in a major city with nothing to do. To pass the time before her next assignment, she often visits museums. She does not have any formal background in art, and would rather spend her time at home with her children than reading books on art. Because she’s usually away for work in random cities, she doesn’t always have friends to go to museums with, but she still wants to discuss the art with “regular” people and potentially scholars if they use colloquial language. At her next stop in Toledo, she visits an art museum, and finds a really interesting abstract art piece that she doesn’t quite understand. She doesn’t really want to spend time reading about background information; she finds that process kind of boring. Instead, she navigates to the artwork’s profile on the app, and reads about other people’s experiences with the piece. She is fascinated with how others describe their experiences with art, and the language they use to convey their emotions. She is also impressed by the insights she gains by reading responses from scholars who use colloquial language. She is surprised to find that people took on very varied interpretations of the art, and slowly begins to develop the confidence to decide for herself what the artwork means to her. She even adds her own comment, and feels pride in participating in this discussion and adding her own take.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;6-favoriting-artworks---easy-task&quot;&gt;6. &lt;em&gt;Favoriting artworks&lt;/em&gt; - Easy task&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chelsea is an avid art-lover, and loves visiting art museums in her spare time. She visits a new museum that just opened in her city, and stumbles upon a painting that she is immediately entranced by. She wants to remember this artwork somehow, so that she can look back on it later and remember how it made her feel. She uses the app to navigate to the painting’s profile and “favorite” it. That night at home, she thinks more about the painting and other artworks that have impacted her. She pulls up the app to see all of the artworks she’s favorited in the past. She goes through some of them, and nostalgically remembers how she felt at each time, and even thinks about the context in her life when each of these artworks was particularly meaningful to her. As she scrolls through, she notices that most of the artworks she’s favorited have been paintings and abstract art, and feels like she’s learned something about her own personal style of expression through this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;extra-tasks&quot;&gt;Extra Tasks:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;7-breaking-down-formal-art-interpretations-into-understandable-terms---hard-task-existing&quot;&gt;7. &lt;em&gt;Breaking down formal art interpretations into understandable terms&lt;/em&gt; - Hard task (Existing)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Syd has had no formal experience studying art and so is not familiar with the formal terms used to describe art. However, she enjoys going to art museums on the weekend with her friends. On one visit, the pamphlets about the artworks use a lot of formal language she doesn’t understand. She asks her friends what they mean. However, there are some parts that are not understandable to her friends either. In these cases, she uses her phone to google each term, and after identifying appropriate definitions, she is able to piece together what the pamphlet is talking about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;8-artist-communicating-with-people-interested-in-her-work---moderate-task-new&quot;&gt;8. &lt;em&gt;Artist communicating with people interested in her work&lt;/em&gt; - Moderate task (New)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jordan Mitchell is a rising modern artist with a number of nationwide exhibitions. Her artwork is revolutionary and can be hard to understand for both art novices and experts. She often attends museum events, explains her work, and interacts with people interested in her work. However, she is unable to attend as many events as she would like to. She communicates with both novice and experienced museum goers. She is able to explain her work, and respond to any of their questions. This helps breakdown the barriers preventing people to understand her revolutionary artwork. It is also a way for Jordan to get real time feedback on how people see her artworks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;first-design&quot;&gt;First Design&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/steph-sketch-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Stephanie’s Sketch&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Sketch of first design&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tasks:&lt;/strong&gt; Background information, contexts, discussion, favoriting, and remembering&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Main Idea:&lt;/strong&gt; This design focuses on how we might layout a particular “art profile” and the discovery of new information about the artwork, as well as user and artist profiles. The artwork is presented as a central page, where “about”, “learn more”, and “discussion” are the main focuses and the user can tab between them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Tasks 1 &amp;amp; 4) Learning:&lt;/strong&gt; The “about” tab includes placard-like explanation. The “learn more” tab on the artwork’s profile allows the user to make an individual choice about which aspect of the background information she’d like to explore. For further exploration, there will be a series of different aspects of the artwork’s background info. Elliot, who likes history, can specifically choose the history tab. In addition, there is a small “progress bar” at the bottom that allows the user to navigate to more information if their curiosity is not yet satisfied. Logan, who wants to learn about the inspiration, can navigate to the “inspiration” section.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Tasks 2, 5, 8) &lt;em&gt;Discussion:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; The “discussion” tab on the artwork’s profile allows the users to talk with each other and with scholars and artists in the field to learn about the artwork in a more informal/colloquial setting. Both Anna and Caroline can use this functionality to hear about others’ experiences. The scholars/artists who participate in the discussion will have special annotations on their icons to indicate that they are professionals in their field, and the particular artist of the work will have a distinct icon so they can reliably answer questions that come up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Task 6) &lt;em&gt;Favoriting Artworks:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; On the “art profile,” there is a button on the upper-right corner (the heart) that allows the users to favorite the work they are looking at. In addition, on the user profile page, Chelsea can look through her past favorites in the “favorites” tab, and also look at an overview of what her favorite pieces were like in the “about” tab. The “about” tab will show her what the breakdown of her favorite artworks is, by genre, time period, or possibly any number of things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Task 3) &lt;em&gt;Remembering Artworks:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; In the user profile, there will be a tab for “favorites.” The user can then look through the artworks they favorited and reflect on what they’ve enjoyed the most in the past. Carlos can use this functionality to keep tabs on all his favorite works, and learn more about them from the comfort of his own home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;second-design&quot;&gt;Second Design&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tasks:&lt;/strong&gt; finding background information, breaking down formal art terms, getting more context,
artist communicating with people about the work&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Main Idea:&lt;/strong&gt; This design is museum-centric. The mobile application is museum-specific and primarily for real-time use while visiting museums. The design allows users to more easily access information about art pieces that are sometimes available in museums, currently in the form of wall text and pamphlets, but now more directly in a centralized source. It provides streamlined, simple information about the piece. This design provides a text search option, a QR code search option, favorites page, and a location-based map of the museum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/joyce-sketch-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Joyce’s Sketch&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Sketch of second design: Main navigation&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Task 1) &lt;em&gt;Reading placards and finding background information about artworks:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
The search and QR scan options allow users to quickly find the pages for artworks. All artwork pages include an image of the work and ID information, such as title, artist, date, etc, that might usually be placed on placards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/joyce-sketch-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Joyce’s Sketch 2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Sketch of second design: Art Profile&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Tasks 1 &amp;amp; 4) &lt;em&gt;Understanding more context about art pieces:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
Scrolling down the Artwork Page reveals a two-tab menu option with “Description” (a brief analysis/explanation of the work) and “Artist” (an artist’s statement on the piece). Elliot and Logan can choose the “Description” tab when they want to learn more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Task 7) &lt;em&gt;Breaking down formal art interpretations into understandable terms:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
The “Description” tab also includes links to basic terms, such as “Surrealism,” which links to a nested page with a definition of the term in easy-to-understand language that Syd can use to develop more understanding about art.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Task 8) &lt;em&gt;Artist communicating to people interested in her work:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
The artist tab includes what the artist would like his/her audience to know about the specific work. Jordan can use this to explain additional information if questions come up. If the artist is current enough, the artist name links to a nested Artist Page, where background information about the artist is provided.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;third-design&quot;&gt;Third Design&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/cliff-sketch-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Cliff’s Sketch&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Sketch of third design&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tasks:&lt;/strong&gt; Understanding more context about art, discussing art with museum experts and novices, Finding background information about art.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Main Idea:&lt;/strong&gt; This design is focused connecting the artist to the museum-goer to enhance the latter’s understanding of an artist’s work. It also introduces a digital space to chat with the artist, other museum-goers, and art experts. The design is designed to be mobile-centric.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Task 4) &lt;em&gt;Understanding Context:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; The main page shows an artist’s profile. It goes into more depth than the traditional wall text or placard. At the top of the page is the artists name, below that we have the image of the artist. The image is followed by a link to the artist’s works. A brief but thorough description of the artist forms the main content of the page. A museum goer like Logan who wants to get more context about an artwork can get more context about an artwork by getting insights from the artists biography.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Task 1) &lt;em&gt;Background Information:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; After clicking the “works” link indicated above, a user is presented with a picture gallery of all the works by an artist. A user like Elliot who wants to understand the background of an artwork can see an artist’s work in relation to other works by the same artist. Clicking on an artwork will further lead to a page about the artwork and offers more detail and context.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Task 2) &lt;em&gt;Discussion with fellow museum-goers:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Below an artwork’s description is a chat bubble with a link that leads to a digital space that fosters discussion among the artist, museum-goers, and scholars in the field. The user is able to ask question about an artwork and respond to other users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(Task 5 &amp;amp; 8) &lt;em&gt;Discussion with experts and artist:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; On top of the discussion page is a list of most recent answers from an artist. Below that is a list of experts. A user can read past discussion and post questions. He is able to interact with both the artist and experts (if he chooses to).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;citations&quot;&gt;Citations&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.loc.gov/rr/print/list/128_migm.html&quot;&gt;Dorothea Lange’s “Migrant Mother” Photographs in the Farm Security Administration Collection: An Overview&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Task Review</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/task-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Task Review" /><published>2018-03-04T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-03-04T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/task-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/task-review/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;existing-tasks&quot;&gt;Existing Tasks:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;reading-placards-and-finding-background-information-about-artworks---hard-task&quot;&gt;Reading placards and finding background information about artworks - Hard task&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Elliot is a junior majoring in history at Amherst. He likes going to museums to learn about history from a visual perspective, and he decides to attend a local art museum on the weekend. He sees an 18th century piece he really likes and reads the placard, but it names only the artist, date, and title of the work, and there is only explanatory wall text for the featured exhibits. He appreciates the art for what it is but feels he is missing part of the puzzle by not knowing anything about the connection between the artist and the work, and especially the history behind it. He writes down the name of the artwork for later, and continues on. When he returns from the museum, he googles the title of the piece hoping to learn more about it. Unfortunately, the artwork he liked so much was made by a lesser-known artist, so there isn’t much on the Internet about it. He does find a few scholarly articles about the artist, but they’re filled with confusing language and art terminology that he doesn’t understand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;discussing-art-with-others-in-person---moderate-task&quot;&gt;Discussing art with others in person - Moderate task&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anna is a frequent attender of museums, and likes to explore new kinds of art. She visits a contemporary art exhibit with a group of friends in a new city. As they’re walking around, a passer-by suggests they go up close to look at the exhibit featuring mirrors, because it provides a different perspective. As they take turns looking at themselves in the reflections, they share thoughts about the experience. Her friend Trevor comments that seeing his reflection in a kaleidoscope way makes him feel uneasy; he’s not used to looking at himself so closely and from so many different angles at the same time. Anna notes that looking at her face within an art installation forces her to view herself in new ways. She feels like she’s looking at herself from an outsider’s perspective. Her friend Jenny then asks a museum staffer how the installation was created, and they have a discussion about where the installation is from and how it was installed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;appreciating-and-remembering-art-after-a-museum-visit---easy-task&quot;&gt;Appreciating and remembering art after a museum visit - Easy task&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Carlos loves visiting museums, and he finds that certain artworks spark something in him that he just can’t describe. For these pieces, he tries to write them down somewhere so he can remember them for later–sometimes in a journal, sometimes in his “Notes” app on his phone. If the piece is part of a permanent exhibit, he jots that down too so he can visit it again the next time he comes to that museum. He also sometimes buys postcards or artist booklets at the museum so he can appreciate the art and look back on it even after he’s left the museum, but those can get pretty expensive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;new-tasks&quot;&gt;New Tasks:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;understanding-more-context-about-art-pieces---hard-task&quot;&gt;Understanding more context about art pieces - Hard task&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Logan is visiting New York and decides to visit the famous MoMA, but he doesn’t know much about art and has no formal art training. He’s looking at the famous “Migrant Mother” photograph, and the placard notes that it was taken in 1963 in Nipomo, California by Dorothea Lange, but he gets no other information. He can feel the desperation in the image, but wants to learn more. Who is the woman in the photograph and why does she look like she’s suffering? He navigates to the photograph’s profile on the app and reads some basic information about the artwork. He learns that Lange was spending a month photographing migratory farm labor when she took this shot. He reads Lange’s account of her experience, and learns that the mother in the photograph “said that they had been living on frozen vegetables from the surrounding fields, and birds that the children killed. She had just sold the tires from her car to buy food.”&lt;sup&gt;[1]&lt;/sup&gt; Logan feels like he can now better understand the emotional energy of the photograph.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;discussing-art-with-museum-experts-and-novices---moderate-task&quot;&gt;Discussing art with museum experts and novices - Moderate task&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Caroline is a flight attendant for a major airline company. Every now and then she finds herself stuck in a major city with nothing to do. To pass the time before her next assignment, she often visits museums. She does not have any formal background in art, and would rather spend her time at home with her children than reading books on art. Because she’s usually away for work in random cities, she doesn’t always have friends to go to museums with, but she still wants to discuss the art with “regular” people who aren’t scholars or curators. At her next stop in Toledo, she visits an art museum, and finds a really interesting abstract art piece that she doesn’t quite understand. She doesn’t really want to spend time reading about background information; she finds that process kind of boring. Instead, she navigates to the artwork’s profile on the app, and reads about other people’s experiences with the piece. She is fascinated with how others describe their experiences with art, and the language they use to convey their emotions. She is surprised to find that people took on very varied interpretations of the art, and slowly begins to develop the confidence to decide for herself what the artwork means to her. She even adds her own comment, and feels pride in participating in this discussion and adding her own take.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;favoriting-artworks---easy-task&quot;&gt;Favoriting artworks - Easy task&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chelsea is an avid art-lover, and loves visiting art museums in her spare time. She visits a new museum that just opened in her city, and stumbles upon a painting that she is immediately entranced by. She wants to remember this artwork somehow, so that she can look back on it later and remember how it made her feel. She uses the app to navigate to the painting’s profile and “favorite” it. That night at home, she thinks more about the painting and other artworks that have impacted her. She pulls up the app to see all of the artworks she’s favorited in the past. She goes through some of them, and nostalgically remembers how she felt at each time, and even thinks about the context in her life when each of these artworks was particularly meaningful to her. As she scrolls through, she notices that most of the artworks she’s favorited have been paintings and abstract art, and feels like she’s learned something about her own personal style of expression through this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;citations&quot;&gt;Citations&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.loc.gov/rr/print/list/128_migm.html&quot;&gt;Dorothea Lange’s “Migrant Mother” Photographs in the Farm Security Administration Collection: An Overview&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Contextual Inquiry Review</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/contextual-inquiry-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Contextual Inquiry Review" /><published>2018-02-28T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-02-28T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/contextual-inquiry-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/contextual-inquiry-review/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;key-findings--takeaways&quot;&gt;Key Findings &amp;amp; Takeaways&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have thus far conducted four different interviews, and are planning on at least one more by the end of the week. We’ve uncovered a lot of information about people’s experience with art in the process. We learned that people often view art in relation to their lives, and that for some people with no formal art background, drawing similarities to different aspects of their lives is how they interact with it. In that vain, we also learned that direction is sometimes needed to guide social conversations about art, to prevent them from devolving into mere speculation. We also learned that navigating a museum’s exhibits correctly is an important part of the museum experience, and that different genres of art should be treated differently (some art is consumed together, as an exhibit, others individually). We learned that information can enhance the museum experience, but too much information can also distract the viewer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;process&quot;&gt;Process&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have performed most of our inquiries as a combination of a semi-structured interview and a traditional contextual inquiry. Since our app is not meant to replace an existing practice as much as provide a new feature and aspect to engagement with art, we found that the traditional contextual inquiry would not be enough for us. Instead, we started our inquiries with semi-structured interviews to get a sense of the user and their experience with art and museums in generals, and then moved to simply observing what users would say to us in real time about different art pieces to glean some understanding of what kinds of questions they might want answered and what their perspective on different art pieces was.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;contextual-inquiry-participants&quot;&gt;Contextual Inquiry Participants&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our first contextual inquiry participant was an Art History professor at the University of Rochester. We interviewed her at MASS MoCA while walking around some exhibits. We noticed her struggle with figuring out how best to navigate exhibits, as there weren’t good directions in the museum. She also noted that although she believes discussion can be helpful in understanding art, there should be some kind of direction in the conversation or else it devolves into speculation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our second participant was actually a couple, two students from MCLA and Worcester State University. We interviewed them at MASS MoCA while walking around the James Turrell exhibit. They were both somewhat interested in art, but had no formal training in Art or Art History. Because they had no formal education in art, I noticed that many of their comments were about art in relation to different things in their lives (many “this reminds me of…” comments). In addition, they learned a lot through museum staff and other museum-goers about the exhibits, but didn’t spend much time reading placards or pamphlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our third participant was a Williams student who occasionally visits museums and has an interest in art, but has no formal background knowledge. He expressed a particular frustration with contemporary, conceptual art that doesn’t allow him to engage in the subject matter as much as less abstract, traditional pieces. This has led him to pay less attention to contemporary art. However, he wouldn’t necessarily want a very formal understanding of art and likes to leave some of his understanding to individual interpretation. Additionally, in order to probe what the current process for learning about art looks like, we conducted a contextual inquiry, asking him to describe his process looking at a few modern pieces. After looking at a Jackson Pollack and not gleaning much from the work, he continued to search for more information on his own. His search evinced the difficulty both in finding a trustworthy, centralized resource for art and in comprehending the language of formal art terms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our fourth contextual inquiry was with an elderly couple. They were looking at a modern art installation about violence. One mentioned that he was an engineer and he could not understand modern art. The other indicated that the museum pamphlets helped them make sense of the art. Although they did not have a full understanding of the exhibit, it was clear that it had an effect on the couple. They were not very comfortable with modern art, and they felt their experience needed to be directed. The couple visits museums every couple months, and they have never had trouble interpreting traditional art.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our fifth contextual inquiry was with Alice and Bob (names changed), a young couple at MASS MoCA. They were observing a large modern art installation. They did not have any formal background in art. Their interest in art was casual, and they visit museums about 6 times a year. We noticed that the couple felt very strongly about art. They expressed that art helped them make sense of their lives. They connect art to their everyday life. Their museum experience was very personal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/affinity-diagram.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Affinity Diagram&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Affinity Diagram&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;contextual-inquiry-themes-and-process&quot;&gt;Contextual Inquiry Themes and Process&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From our contextual inquiries, we:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Confirmed that learning is the ultimate goal for art museum-goers&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Discovered these learning experiences are unique to the individual,&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;And so resources that support this endeavor must be customizable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learning as the primary goal of museum-goers reinforces the necessity of a more accessible resource, which was our initial intuition. The presence of context and background information on art are integral to this learning process. Our inquiries also illuminated the current lack of such a convenient resource that appropriately communicates context. The current gap in information disclosure is due to the limited physical space in museums to disseminate information to users in the form of placards and wall text, and to the inconvenient and often unused circulation of pamphlets. This apparent mismatch in communicating context confirms the motivation for our design solution. In addition, social discussion is only one aspect of learning, but is a crucial part in gaining new knowledge in an informal way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also uncovered on a high level the nature of the learning experience when it comes to art. Because we are dealing with the subjective experience of enjoying art, the entire journey of art learning at museums must also accommodate a range of individual experiences. This personalization must be considered at all points of the learning experience, starting with the initial art background and interest level of the users to how and what they aim to learn. We learned that people enjoy relating art back to their own lives, so they must be able to practice individuality when engaging with any kind of art. In wanting to maintain their autonomy, they may explicitly choose not to learn too much background information about an art piece, and may simply want to engage with it themselves. Users must be able to make this choice for themselves. Social discussion plays a large part in this; it allows users to participate in an informal discussion about art that allows them to gain new knowledge, and yet it still allows them to express their individually. An example of this is when we noticed museum-goers asking museum staff specific questions about art pieces. This was one avenue through which they were able to tailor the amount of background knowledge they wanted to their needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through affinity diagramming, we were able to identify these high-level themes, as shown by the pink and purple post-its in the diagram above. By grouping similar statements from our interviewees together, we were able to pinpoint commonalities in the learning experience in art museums. For example, we noticed that the Art History professor stated that placards are informative but can be distracting, and actually both students noted that too much background information can actually take away from their appreciation of an artwork. To us, this meant that users would want to customize and tailor their learning to fit their needs. We used this kind of process to move from specific statements by specific users to general statements about groups of users throughout the construction of our affinity diagram.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;task-analysis&quot;&gt;Task Analysis&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Who is going to use the design?&lt;/em&gt;
Our main target users will be people who are interested in art and enjoy going to museums, but don’t necessarily have any formal background or training in art. We would also like to target users who study art formally, such as students, Art History professors and researchers, etc. We think their input will provide a valuable source of information for the general discussions on artworks, and may help guide the conversations in more productive ways. Lastly, we want to involve museum curators in the process, to allow them to tailor “art profiles” based on the layouts of the exhibits and to provide relevant information (the same kind of information they might currently provide in pamphlets scattered throughout the museum).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;What tasks do they now perform?&lt;/em&gt;
In the museum, users are currently able to glean information from placards, wall text/artist bios, and pamphlets. They can engage with the art in a more social way by talking to their friends, other museum-goers, or museum staff. Outside the museum, users interested in art might perform informal individual searches on art pieces or artists to learn extra information. Museum curators are responsible for putting together exhibits, deciding what kinds of information to put in artists bios and placards and what to leave out, and deciding whether to include additional pamphlets.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;What tasks are desired?&lt;/em&gt; 
Users should be able to gain new knowledge about different pieces of art at their own pace. Users should be able to learn about artists, their inspiration, and any other relevant information about the piece. Users should be able to comment on artworks, read about others’ perspectives, and reply to others’ comments to spark a conversation. Users should be able to individualize their experience and feel personally connected to the art. This could mean being able to save artworks as “favorites,” or something else. Curators should be able to update information about exhibits, remove intolerant comments, provide helpful background information, and engage with the users themselves.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;How are the tasks learned?&lt;/em&gt; 
Because our product will be in the form of a mobile/web application, the learning process for users should be relatively straightforward. We will try to make the interface similar to other social interfaces to make the adoption very seamless. However, because this is an app for all ages, the tasks may also be learned at the museum (museum staff could be trained to teach a basic outline of how to use the app, if needed). If the museum curator aspect gets more complicated, learning will be at the design level (e.g. a short tutorial at the beginning).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Where are the tasks performed?&lt;/em&gt;
The main focus will be users navigating museums, but there are additional use cases where the user might want to look back on exhibits he’s viewed in the past and comment on them, so we don’t restrict location. In addition, users may want to use the data as a resource for learning outside the museum. Curators will naturally be performing tasks at the museum or in their offices when planning out new exhibits.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;What is the relationship between the person and data?&lt;/em&gt;
Because this is an online forum and we would like to limit intolerant behavior, comments will be public and linked to the person’s profile, but we will collect limited data about the person, and only as much as the user is willing to provide (we will not require much). The data regarding user comments should persist at least throughout the lifetime of the exhibit, and may be archived after. The data the museum curator provides (through background information, pictures, etc.) can be controlled by the curator herself, and she may archive or delete the data as she sees fit. Data should be updated frequently to bring up the newest comments and spark ongoing conversation.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;What other tools does the person have?&lt;/em&gt;
Placards and pamphlets throughout museums are the current tools people have to learn new information about art and artists in museums. In addition, they have museum staff and other museum-goers to talk to. To establish individual relationships with art, users currently can buy postcards at museum gift shops as memorabilia of their favorite works. To learn additional information, users can also look up background information on artists or exhibits on their phone, but this may be a rather inefficient way of finding the relevant information.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;How do people communicate with each other?&lt;/em&gt;
Users will be able to leave comments, similar to comments sections in other social places (like Reddit, Youtube, etc.). They will be able to reply to others’ comments, start new comments, and read others’ perspectives. Users who have studied art formally will play a special role in this conversation, and may help guide the discussion or else inform the discussion with relevant background.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;How often are the tasks performed?&lt;/em&gt;
From our survey data, people seem to visit museums once a month to once a year, and this is when we’d expect people to perform the tasks most often. For museum curators, exhibits change frequently and the curators may want to regularly catch up with how users are reacting to their different exhibits.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;What are the time constraints on the tasks?&lt;/em&gt;
There aren’t any hard constraints on the tasks here, but since people spend limited time at a museum, they will likely not spend too much time on each individual “art profile.” How much time they do choose to spend will depend on the complexity of the art piece to the user and how interested the user is in that particular work. For the museum curators, there also won’t be any hard constraints, but we imagine they will want to be able to complete their tasks quickly and smoothly.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;What happens when things go wrong?&lt;/em&gt;
Fake news (spreading of false information masquerading as facts), conversations devolving into mere speculations rather than a genuine understanding of the art, and intolerant behavior or hate speech that is unproductive and uninformative (trolls).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Contextual Inquiry Check-In</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/contextual-inquiry-check-in/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Contextual Inquiry Check-In" /><published>2018-02-25T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-02-25T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/contextual-inquiry-check-in</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/contextual-inquiry-check-in/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;setup&quot;&gt;Setup&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our entire team went to MASS MoCA on Saturday and each interviewed a different demographic for about 30 minutes to an hour each.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;interviews&quot;&gt;Interviews&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;group-a&quot;&gt;Group A:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Demographic:&lt;/em&gt; Two students, aged 19 and 21, at MCLA and Worcester State University.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Background:&lt;/em&gt; Both students had some experience with art, with one being only tangentially interested in art, going to museums around once a year, and the other (at MCLA) visiting MASS MoCA whenever there was a new exhibit, but both not having any formal art history background.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Insights:&lt;/em&gt; As I walked around the museum with them, I noticed that because they didn’t have much art history background, they mostly commented on what different artworks reminded them of (eg. “the lights look like the aurora borealis”). I also noticed that they got tips or insights from others in the museum and the museum staff. As we walked into one exhibit, an older man suggested we “get up close and look at it from the side.” In a Turrell exhibit, they asked a staffer “how big is the room?” and “how did they create the hazy effect?”. Their questions about the different artworks were mostly where the inspiration came from, but they noted that they just wanted some and not too much information because “just a little bit of background information can spark your imagination.” The Turrell exhibit also made me realize that some exhibits don’t allow photos, so we may want to think about a new way of recognizing which exhibits people are in. I also noticed that many artworks in MASS MoCA are not intended to be consumed piece by piece, but rather as an entire exhibit, so it may make more sense in some cases to set up our “art profiles” by exhibit rather than artwork.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Issues:&lt;/em&gt; I found that I wanted to probe them with more questions about the art, but I also didn’t want to steer their understanding of art in one way or another. For example, I wanted to know what kinds of background information they were interested in, but I felt like if I directly asked “would you want to know how modern art slowly evolved into different pieces like this?” or “would you be curious about related artists?” I would automatically get a “yes” answer even if they didn’t, so I didn’t know how to approach that. I didn’t have any difficulty establishing rapport, but I think that was made easier because the two were my age.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;group-b&quot;&gt;Group B:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A young couple who expressed a casual interest in art, one noted that art for him was “another lens for him to understand his place in life” and “a stimulus to spark a reflection on himself”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;group-c&quot;&gt;Group C:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An elderly couple who noted that they preferred traditional art, and read the pamphlets at MASS MoCA because they couldn’t understand modern art.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;going-forward&quot;&gt;Going Forward&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We plan to interview at least two more people, a student at Williams and an art history professor. The interview with the student is currently set for Monday. The interviews with both the student and professor will hopefully be at WCMA if they have time, so we can have some probes handy to ask specific questions. We will try to use tape recorders for the next interviews (if they’re okay with it), because we found that it was difficult to jot notes down while standing at the museum. We need to plan more “go-to” questions as well; we wanted to do the interviews very unstructured, but found it was hard to come up with the right phrasing for questions we wanted on the spot. We may also see if we can get another professor or student to do some journaling at a museum for us (documenting their opinions on different artworks), but this is definitely more time-intensive for them.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Contextual Inquiry Plan</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/contextual-inquiry-plan/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Contextual Inquiry Plan" /><published>2018-02-21T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-02-21T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/contextual-inquiry-plan</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/contextual-inquiry-plan/">&lt;p&gt;Our design aims to promote a more inclusive community centered around public art. Our target users are those who lack the formal background knowledge to more deeply appreciate and learn about art pieces seen in museums. 
Providing a resource that allows people to learn more about and discuss art also creates a valuable information source for general use and research. The potentially multi-faceted application of our design broadens our users to include not only those who don’t know much about art but also those who do–such as art historians and the artists themselves. We plan to conduct contextual inquiries on the following subjects:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Art History Professor. Art history professors at Williams are not only passionate about but also have years of experience engaging and teaching students with no previous background in art. We have already reached out to one professor, and are currently awaiting a response. The interview will be conducted in the professor’s office sometime early next week. We have some backup professors lined up too, since we are all in Art history classes this semester.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A student. We would like to target a student that has visited museums in his lifetime and is interested in art, but does not yet have any background knowledge. We have reached out to a friend of Joyce’s, so Stephanie/Cliff will conduct the interview.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Random museum-goers. We plan to sit in a museum like MASS MoCA, and survey individuals who are carefully looking at art pieces. We will sit in the last room of Tanja Hollander’s exhibit; it provides a nice space with sofas and tables, allows conversation, and already provokes interaction with the art. We will also spend some time candidly observing people visiting the museum, and will record how often they stop to look at artworks and whether groups of visitors spend time discussing various artworks with each other.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will be conducting our interviews in multiple settings, as mentioned above. The location for the student interview will be Tunnel City because it provides a casual and familiar atmosphere, and features various artworks on the walls. We will use a semi-structured interview style, because we are still in the exploratory stage. We will start our interviews with a brief introduction to our project proposal, but then quickly steer the conversation to broader probing questions about the interviewee’s relationship to art. We will be observing people at the museum, but for the one-on-one interviews we will ask them questions about how often they engage with art, how they engage, what their opinions are on the art world, and what they’d like to learn about art. Potential questions include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How often do you visit museums?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How much do you know about art?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We will probe each interviewee with the same piece of art, and ask them what their first reactions are, to get a sense of how different people will comment on the art in the app.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the Professor:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How do you think people should look at art?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What do you feel is the value in informal evaluations of art?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How helpful are discussions to an understanding of art?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author><summary type="html">Our design aims to promote a more inclusive community centered around public art. Our target users are those who lack the formal background knowledge to more deeply appreciate and learn about art pieces seen in museums. Providing a resource that allows people to learn more about and discuss art also creates a valuable information source for general use and research. The potentially multi-faceted application of our design broadens our users to include not only those who don’t know much about art but also those who do–such as art historians and the artists themselves. We plan to conduct contextual inquiries on the following subjects:</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Project Ideation</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/project-ideation/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Project Ideation" /><published>2018-02-19T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-02-19T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/project-ideation</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/project-ideation/">&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/IMG_4274.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Joyce ideation&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Joyce's ideation pic&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/IMG_4275.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Cliff ideation&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Cliff's ideation pic&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/ideation-sliu1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Steph's ideation 1&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/ideation-sliu2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Steph's ideation 2&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Stephanie's ideation pics&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Team Contract</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/team-contract/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Team Contract" /><published>2018-02-18T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-02-18T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/team-contract</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/team-contract/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;1-team-contact-information&quot;&gt;1. TEAM CONTACT INFORMATION&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The group will communicate through GroupMe and/or Facebook Messenger. Urgent matters may be communicated through email. Joyce has commitments for NBC at night, so we’ll usually meet during the day. We are sharing our Google Calendars so we get an idea of when we’re all free. Our goal is to create a great project we’re proud of in the end!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;2-guiding-principles&quot;&gt;2. GUIDING PRINCIPLES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We will work as a team, and less as a working group.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We will create a collaborative learning environment that is comfortable for everyone.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We want everyone to feel satisfied with and proud of their individual contributions.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We will be invested in the success of this project.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We will put the team’s needs before individual needs (there’s no I in team!).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;3-preliminary-focus-on-purpose&quot;&gt;3. PRELIMINARY FOCUS ON PURPOSE&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The goal of this project is to bring art engagement to people who would otherwise be intimidated by art. We want to make art accessible by creating a user-friendly and welcoming platform for discussions. Our customer-base will be anyone who is familiar with tech and sees value in participating in online forums for art.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;4-group-roles&quot;&gt;4. GROUP ROLES&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are all generalists and all members are expected to prepare for meetings, participate in meetings, complete assigned tasks, and support the efforts of other team members.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Group roles will be assigned on a case-by-case basis. They will be determined by assigned tasks. Every member is a leader and should conduct themselves as such. It is the responsibility of all members to be aware of what needs to be done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;5-dividing-up-the-task--the-division-of-labor&quot;&gt;5. DIVIDING UP THE TASK:  THE DIVISION OF LABOR&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tasks will be divided according to expressed strengths and weaknesses, or desires.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We will divide the work by action items/deadlines and balance among members.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Everyone should contribute equally, but members are encouraged to volunteer for the assignments they are most interested in or think they can contribute the most to.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Everyone will work to look over finished assignments or projects before the final push.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;6-team-plan&quot;&gt;6. TEAM PLAN&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the beginning of every meeting we will set-up a weekly plan. This plan will depend on the project requirements of the professor, and the assigned tasks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;7-meeting-management&quot;&gt;7. MEETING MANAGEMENT&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will meet as needed, but at least once a week. The location of the meeting will be determined through GroupMe and/or at the previous meeting. Meetings will be scheduled according to common free times in the Google Calendar, and the length will be determined by the tasks to be addressed. Attendance is mandatory. It is the responsibility of members to communicate ahead of time if they are to be late or will miss a scheduled meeting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During meetings we will reinforce positive attitudes and constructively deal with problems. The focus of the task will be determined by the requirements and direction of the class instructor. Members are encouraged to offer constructive suggestions, comments and criticism. One person will talk at a time. Group members should pay attention and stick to the agenda at hand. All members will contribute to the meeting. Decisions are determined by majority rule. Conflicts will be solved through negotiation and understanding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;8-accountability-process&quot;&gt;8. ACCOUNTABILITY PROCESS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Completed tasks are presented at the beginning of every meeting.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If a group member encounters a challenge while completing a task, they should inform other members before the next meeting.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If a group member is unable to complete a task before a set meeting, he/she should inform the others with plenty of time in advance.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We will schedule intermediate peer review meetings for larger projects.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Project benchmarks will be task specific and will be determined on a case-by-case basis. They are assigned at the conclusion of every meeting. Members are expected to meet and/or exceed benchmarks.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Completed tasks are reviewed by all group members at the beginning of every meeting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;9-rewards-and-punishments&quot;&gt;9. REWARDS AND PUNISHMENTS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The group will accept feedback both negative and positive.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Points will be determined by member contribution which we expect to be equal.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We will celebrate team success through high fives.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We reward individual initiative and contribution by giving compliments.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We handle non-performance and failure to meet commitments through communication. All group members should be open to constructive criticism.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Behavior that disrupts group function should be communicated and addressed during group meetings, and can be brought up by anyone in the team.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Negative internal feedback should not be viewed as personal, and is meant to improve the performance of the team as a whole. External feedback applies to all group members, not any particular member.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;10-follow-up&quot;&gt;10. FOLLOW-UP&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The contract will be revised as the team majority sees fit.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Issues that are not covered in the contract will be decided through majority rule, and they will be incorporated into the contract.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry><entry><title type="html">Project Proposal</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/project-proposal/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Project Proposal" /><published>2018-02-18T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-02-18T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hciproject/project-proposal</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hciproject/project-proposal/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;motivation&quot;&gt;Motivation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On a recent visit to MASS MoCA, I came across Tanja Hollander’s “Are you really my friend?” exhibit. &lt;sup&gt;[1]&lt;/sup&gt; At the end of the exhibit, there’s a room with a wall of post-it notes trying to answer the question “What is a true friend?”. Next to the wall, there are a few sofas and desks, and a stack of post-it notes for museum-goers to add on to the collection. As I watched other people in the room sit down and scribble down thoughts, I was struck by just how accessible this exhibit was. Everyone could relate to it, and even kids were jotting down ideas and contributing to the process. Our proposal builds off this idea of breaking down the elusive nature of art engagement and creating a more interactive and inclusive experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;../assets/images/massmoca.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mass MoCA post its&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Post-its at the MASS MoCA exhibit&lt;sup&gt;[1]&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-problem&quot;&gt;The Problem&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Art provides a medium for self-expression that relates people and their experiences in an inherently human way. Art museums, a primary resource for learning about and experiencing art, are meant to invite the general public and people to engage in this creative dialogue. However, this conversation about art can feel intimidatingly inaccessible for the general public. For regular people, who aren’t academics or involved in the “art world,” art can feel elusive, out-of-touch, or even perhaps just confusing. In fact, the homogeneity of the art world is a well-documented and studied problem, where “among those who frequented art museums, a stunning 92 percent identified as white, and only 16 percent identified as a minority.”&lt;sup&gt;[2]&lt;/sup&gt;  Without a formal introduction to art, which is generally only available to the privileged, it’s hard to glean a lot of insight from the works in front of you. Part of this problem is both the little information provided by the display of works at museums and the lack of informal resources for engaging in conversations about art.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-proposal&quot;&gt;The Proposal&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our proposal aims at exploring new ways to interact with art by allowing users to share experiences and information about the pieces through a digital platform. While looking around at museums, users can, with their phones, take a picture of a piece of art (or simply type in the name) and pull up that piece of art’s “profile” on their mobile device.&lt;br /&gt;
The profile would serve to provide any lacking foundational background information about the piece and facilitate social discussion for forming new outlooks and perspectives about the art.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;background-information&quot;&gt;Background information&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the placards and artists bios displayed with works at museums are helpful, most pieces themselves only have a small placard listing the artist, date, and perhaps who it was donated by. We think many people would “understand” art better by learning about the artist’s motivations and intentions. This app would allow museum-goers to easily pull up background information about any piece of art, and thereby explore new art through a “related artists” section. Users could also learn about what this “genre” of art is, how/where/why it developed, and thereby begin to develop a vocabulary about art in general. The app could also offer suggestions based on what kinds of art the user has bookmarked, and thus allow the user to constantly explore new art even after they’ve left the museum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;social-discussion&quot;&gt;Social Discussion&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since art is never meant to be a solitary but a social human experience, the “comments section” on a piece of art creates a space for informal discussion and creating new knowledge with other passionate individuals. Users can read comments from other users, make their own comment about how different pieces impact them their opinions, and save the piece (like a bookmark), or share it on social media.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This space allows the art museum experience to move from a conversation between the curator and the museum-goer, to a conversation between “regular people.” It allows users to learn about art through the experiences of other people, which is valuable to an understanding of what art is. We don’t want our museums to feel “stuffy” and pretentious; that’s how we end up with a homogenous museum-going base. It also allows users to feel connected to art, by allowing them to define their individuality in finding specific pieces more impactful, saving those pieces, and being able to go back and look at their collection later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;sources&quot;&gt;Sources&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1: &lt;a href=&quot;http://massmoca.org/event/tanja-hollander/&quot;&gt;“Tanja Hollander, Are you really my friend?”: MassMoCA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2: &lt;a href=&quot;http://bigthink.com/Picture-This/does-the-art-world-have-a-demographics-problem&quot;&gt;“Does the art world have a demographics problem?”: Big Think&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Art for All</name></author></entry></feed>